Chapter 6: Lucius Malofy

11:25 pm, June 18th, 1993

Lucius Malfoy woke up in a jolt. He opened his eyes, and saw a smirking Severus Snape towering over him. He looked around haltingly at the obelisks and farmland graveyard.

Lucius remembered being forced to be the binder of the Unbreakable Vow, and pointing his wand at the Boy-Who-Lived, whom the Dark Lord seriously believed might destroy the world. Then the Dark Lord and the Potter boy had had quite an interesting conversation in Parseltongue, where apparently none of them considered the possibility that someone else might understand that language as well.

If Lucius did not feel so upset about losing much of his magic, he might have some sharp remarks on the arrogance of both the Potter boy and the Dark Lord.

But as Lucius had listened to the hisses, he had found that what costed most of his magic was not some bad joke on the Dark Lord's part. Both natural Parselmouths had honestly believed that Harry Potter might really bring an end to this world, possibly using muggle science.

Lucius knew something about muggle science, like the book that Harry Potter lent Draco with pictures of muggles on the moon. When the news that Draco almost died from the blood-cooling charm arrived, Lucius almost went mad. He remembered the horror when he came home and found all his house elves stunned and oblivated, as he ran and called for Narcissa, as he found nothing but burning marks in their bedroom. If it were not for the crying Draco in the cradle, he might have went mad that day. It was like that nightmare all over again. But his boy was OK, and was at home.

However, Lucius did need to know what happened at Hogwarts. And his boy, who once told him everything, refused to really talk. He knew this was a sign of growing up, but he could not risk losing Draco and not knowing. With broken heart, he administered Draco three drops of Veritaserum. And Draco talked, and talked. Compared to what Draco had said, the ravings of lunatics in St. Mungos made much more sense. How could muggles become more powerful than wizards? How could they arrive at the Moon where no wizard had ever landed, using "science"? And blood - according to some weird muggle theory, there was no difference between a pureblood and a muggleborn? All because of how many wizarding children squib couples had? How could that be true? It was a widely known fact that muggleborn couples littered more squibs. And as for squibs giving birth to wizarding kids, who knew whether the filthy female squibs had cheated on their useless squib husbands? Stupid wizards who did not mind producing bastards were still much better than squibs. When Lucius pointed those out to his son, Draco was quite shocked. Lucius sighed: a clever boy as Draco was, he was still too young and gullible, and he did not fully understand the adults' world yet. Yet, although the flaw in the Boy-Who-Lived's blood theory brought Lucius some comfort, the whole moon thing still seemed to be true.

Lucius glanced at the moon uncomfortably.

And then the Boy-Who-Lived threatened the Dark Lord with a massive explosion that could kill everyone.

Lucius was confused, but guessed it might have some moon thing in it. The pictures on that devilish book Harry used to seduce Draco away from him did show huge fire coming from the end of a rocket…

And Lucius' world swirled and he thought he saw his own headless body fell to the ground.

Then everything went dark.

Dark until this moment.

Lucius pushed himself up to a seating position, one hand instinctively went to check his neck, the other fumbled for his wand and failed. As he looked around, and saw himself on an altar that looked quite similar to what his master had created, and it was in a graveyard much smaller than the place he lost consciousness, and there was also the smirking black-haired man, whom Lucius trusted slightly above average. Lucius had no choice but to ask: "Severus, my friend, what happened?"

Severus answered in his broken Parseltongue: "You d-died, and I rev...revived you."

Just as Lucius' brain went blank with the shocking news, Severus waved his wand, and said: "Tempus."

"11:26 pm, June 18th, 1993" appeared in front of Lucius.

Lucius wanted to cast the time revealing charm himself to verify, but found that the once simple charm that he could cast without a wand or a word when he was half asleep failed on him. He had to concentrate and cast again: "Tempus."

"11:26 pm, June 18th, 1993" popped up again.

Lucius swallowed down the hard news, and then realized something worse than his own death: Draco had been an orphan for more than a year. Mr. Macnair, Draco's godfather, was torn into pieces in his open rebellion against the Dark Lord. And Mr. Avery, Draco's fallback godfather...was probably dead as well. And his boy had been a toy for Lord Potter to try his brainwash techniques for more than a year now, that was, if he was lucky. Otherwise…

Lucius did not really want to think what might have happened otherwise.

As if reading Lucius' mind through his perfect occlumency barrier, the towering black-haired wizard hissed: "No v-worry. Nar-cisssa isss alive, with Draco now."

Lucius' mind went blank again.

As Severus began to recount the story on Narcissa from the Daily Prophet in human language, rejoice and relief almost overwhelmed Lucius. Lucius knew that Narcissa's death was Dumbledore's fault as well as his own. He had brought danger home, he had blindly trusted the ancient wards in Malfoy manor, and he had failed to protect Narcissa. He had left the burning marks in their bedroom as a reminder of both his hatred towards Dumbledore and of his own stupidity. Now knowing that Narcissa was obliviated, and was sent to live in Australia as a muggle, though his brain could generate hundreds of ways how this could be used against House Malfoy, Lucius still could not suppress his gratitude towards Dumbledore and the Boy-Who-Lived.

Then there come another big question: why did Severus revive him? True, Severus had been his ally, and they probably trusted each other slightly more than average. But why such trouble? Any similar reason as why the Dark Lord revived the Granger girl? Prophecy or something?

Even though he probably would not get a true answer, Lucius had to ask: "Severus, my dearest friend, why did you resurrect me?"

Lucius deliberately asked in human language, so that his savior with a wand could choose freely whether to answer it in truth or not.

To his shock, Severus answered in Parseltongue: "P…Pl…Prefer you to li-live than die."

Lucius had no idea Severus treasured their "friendship" so much, or at least, to the extent that the black-haired man could honestly say that he preferred Lucius alive. Whatever the other man's hidden motives were, Lucius knew he needed to be really grateful. Plus, the other wizard was much stronger than he was now, and had a wand at hand.

Lucius knew the ways to thank someone who had just saved your life from the brim of death, but he had no idea how to thank a possible true friend who revived you more than a year after you died. And since he had been dead for quite some time, Lucius guessed he no longer had a lot of resources and powers he once wielded.

-True friendship, is that what Severus desired? I guess I can offer him that, at least to the extent of my friendship with Walden Macnair. But friendship alone seems too empty and vague. This half-blood's eyes did light up when he saw gold. That I think I still have some. And he may desire glory and fame, I have heard him talked about Order of Merlin once or twice. Giving him an Order of Merlin was no trouble at all before I died, but now it may require some serious plotting. Well, perhaps only money for now, and an Order of Merlin, First Class later as a surprised gift.

Lucius was no fool. He knew he had dangerous enemies, and had planned for Draco accordingly. He had bought properties in other parts of the world, and had set up some secret vaults in Gringotts' oversea branches. Some of the Malfoy wealth would be available to Draco upon Lucius' death, some would only be known to Draco as he came of age, and some would go to Draco's vault in a monthly basis. Lucius quickly recounted the contents of the secret vaults that Draco didn't know yet, and decided the Mexico City one, which had one hundred thousand galleons, sounded too much like an insult to people in Dumbledore's faction (which Severus had apparently convinced the Boy-Who-Lived that he was in), and the Rome one, which contained something he did not want Severus to know. So, the Tokyo vault.

Lucius made sure shock and gratitude was shown on his face and eyes, and hissed: "Sseveruss, there iss no word that I can desscribe my gratitude toward you. You are my ssavior and true friend. Noble and Most Ancient House or not, House Malfoy recognizess itss life debt to you. I know money iss nothing compared to what you have done, but that can certainly make life a little bit eassier. I have a ssecret vault in Gringottss, in Tokyo, two hundred and fifty thousand galleonss in it, available to anyone with vault number and proper passsword. The vault number iss 122, and the passsword iss," Lucius paused, and then continued, "Cor meum esst intra portass tuass, Draco Meum."

The black-haired wizard smirked upon hearing the vault part, then raised his brow slightly as he heard the probably too sentimental password and Draco's name.

-Well, how can a half-blood possibly know what lies in the "my heart stays with you" statement?

Chapter 9: Return of Father

9:29 am, June 24th, 1993

Draco Malfoy waited anxiously in the guest apparition room alongside with Mother.

The soon-to-be Lord Malfoy received a letter from Gringotts yesterday, stating that Severus Snape had an important message for him from Father, to be delivered upon the event that Draco came to magical majority and became Lord Malfoy.

This was indeed a thing Father would do, and all the secret marks on that letter were right.

Father was always prepared, even for his own death. After Father passed away, Draco received Father's will, one copy from his trusted lawyer and one copy from the goblins, in which Father left the majority of his properties to Draco, entrusted most businesses to professional managers, allocated money that would go to the Crabbes and Goyles on a monthly basis for them to continue their services to House Malfoy, made donations to St. Mungo's to ensure that all Malfoys would be treated in the best possible way, set up a fund for Hogwarts so that Draco would become a member of Hogwarts' Board of Governors after he graduated…

Draco wanted to cry each time he thought of Father's will, of how Father had planned for him. But he had lost more than eighty percent of what Father left him due to the heavy fines to the Ministry of Magic and restitutions to the victims of Father's crimes.

-Who knows if Father did the things people accused him of or not? And since all Death Eaters in Azkaban have went crazy from ten years' exposure to Dementors, there is only one talking mouth now: Igor Karkaroff! Maybe Karkaroff committed some of those crimes himself, and he put them on Father. Or, maybe the victims' family bribed Karkaroff to put everything on Father, so that they can claim restitutions from the rich Malfoys, instead of the knutless Travers.

Draco knew better than to argue with the relatives of the deceased. Instead, Mother and Draco set up a generous fund for the victims' families, and handed the fund management power to Mad-Eye Moody. He secretly hoped that the financial management job would tire out the old auror soon enough, so he would give fewer suspicious stares and try fewer legilimency attempts on Draco each time they came cross. But since youth was being mass produced in Hogwarts, this plot was highly unlikely to work. Of course, neither Mother nor Draco admitted knowing wrong-doing by Father that they knew of - which was true, since Father never mentioned any details - they just said they felt really sorry to the heavy losses of the families.

But losing all that money did not mean Draco and Mother were living in poverty. Father had managed Mother's dowry well over the years, and the value had grew more than ten folds. Draco suspected that Father had put some of the Malfoy wealth into Mother's dowry, so that if things went really wrong and all the Malfoy money got confiscated, Draco would still have something to rely on. Now Mother's dowry was legally returned to Mother, and the returns were more than enough for them to live a really comfortable life.

Additionally, there was money from undisclosed sources coming to Draco's personal vault each month. And Draco suspected there would be a lump sum of money becoming available to him upon his majority and his marriage.

Father really had everything planned.

Father had even arranged for Draco to receive a Firebolt as a present for his thirteenth birthday. When Draco received the fastest racing broomstick the day before he took his OWLS exams, he locked himself in his dorm and cried. In his pre-Hogwarts days, Draco had told Father that he wanted to become a seeker for Slytherin House, just as Father did when he was in Hogwarts. Draco had wanted to make Father proud. And Father had promised Draco the fastest racing broomstick if he became a seeker.

Draco didn't become a seeker, and Father wouldn't know that.

Father wouldn't know that Draco was no longer the child who loved Quidditch and dreamed to become a seeker. Draco needed to keep a close eye on Harry so that the Boy-Who-Lived wouldn't cause an instantaneous wizarding war in his naivety. Draco knew that Harry did not tell him all the secrets Harry shared with Hermione, and Father would not like that. However, a lot of times, Draco was simply too tired to care, all the international politics were more than enough for him.

Father wouldn't be happy if he knew Draco settled himself as the third person in the power structure. But if Harry and Hermione got married someday as everyone said they would, Draco wondered whether that would be counted as him serving the Lord and Lady of the Potter House, and therefore, second in command.

Draco cringed a bit on how disappointed Father would be if he knew Draco's condition, then directed his attention to the incoming messenger.

Draco knew Snape and Father were allies, but he didn't think they were close. Yet, there were a lot of things that Draco didn't know about Father, and it was possible that there was a chain-of-command, and all the people before Snape were dead. And to be honest, Draco held some resentments at Snape for just abandoning Slytherin like that.

Then, a popping sound came from behind the newly installed Thief's Downfall, and the former Head of Slytherin House appeared with no automatic anti-concealment alarms triggered.

The black-haired man looked worse than when he was Head of Slytherin. His hair was as greasy and unkempt as he had not stood in a shower or used a comb for at least a week, his dark eyes were like slow boiling fire, the dark circles below his eyes were quite obvious, his cheek was shallow, and his black robes were spotty, and there were heavy smells of potion coming from him. And the man had a grey suitcase in his left hand, which might contain something that Father wanted Draco to have.

Draco wondered if an extra powerful imperius curse wouldn't be washed off by the Thief's Downfall, or if the man was simply annoyed at getting interrupted in his potion experiments and needing to deliver some message for a dead ally.

Draco instinctively grabbed Father's wand tighter in his hands, and Snape eyed Draco as if in approval of Draco's reaction.

Mother stepped forward, and raised her right hand while holding her wand in her left: "Severus, what a delight to meet you!"

To Draco's slight relief, Snape put his wand into his left hand together with his suitcase, grabbed Mother's hand and made a hasty handshake. "Glad to meet you, too, Lady Malfoy."

The greasy man didn't show any particular interest in the beautiful and rich widow, simply turned to Draco, sizing him up and down for a bit, then said: "Glad to meet you, Mr. Malfoy."

Draco knew he was not Lord Malfoy yet, but that was why Snape was here, wasn't it? Draco smiled politely, and shook hands with the former Potions Master.

Before Mother or Draco could say any more courtesy words, Snape cut in and said: "I would like a place with more privacy for what we are about to converse."

Mother and Draco exchanged a brief glance, and showed Snape to a private study.

"Mr. Malfoy, It is my understanding that you would receive occlumency lessons before entering your magical majority." The man said without sitting down, as if in a hurry. "Not only up to the level that you can fool Veritaserum, but up to the level that you can block Alastor Moody."

Remembering all the "trainings" he got from Moody, Draco answered: "Yes."

And Mother said: "I guess I need to check lunch now. Severus, is there anything that you would like to try?"

Mother was an occlumens for sure, but she probably could not resist a powerful legilimens such as Moody or the Dark Lord, and that's probably one of the reasons why Father never talked of his Death Eater business with her.

Snape mumbled: "Anything would be fine."

After Mother left, Snape put his suitcase down, and casted spell after spell to the room. Some of the spells Draco had learnt from preparing for his OWLS, some Draco had seen Mr. Bester casting before occlumency lessons, and there were about half of them Draco had never heard of.

Snape turned and -

A red-hot blade took its aim toward Draco's mind, and cutting through his layers of occlumency barriers like cutting through shear butter. If it were not for Moody's frequent trials, Draco might lose the grip of his final barrier and reveal all the nights that he cried for Father. But this was way worse than anything Moody had tried, worse than anything Draco had experienced, Draco was barely able to stand.

The pain stopped.

Draco staggered, realizing that he was facing the second most powerful Death Eater, alone. If this man wanted to attack…

Snape raised an eyebrow and said: "Mad-Eye didn't test you hard enough, did he?"

Draco panted. He knew Snape should and would do this if he were going to talk about something really important, but doing THAT to -

Draco heard an unbelievably familiar sound from Snape's suitcase: "Severus, I can't feel my legs!"

Snape cursed and opened his suitcase. As Snape was running down the stairs of the suitcase, Draco could only see the back side of someone crawling on the floor of the study-sized room inside the suitcase. The long white hair, the neatly manicured yet powerful hands, the elegant feeling of the common robes from just being worn by that man, crawling in pain or not...

-No, it can't be…

After Snape threw a number of spells on the figure on the ground, the pain that man had been in seemed to cease. Seeing that man no longer in immediate danger, Draco let out a breath that he hadn't quite realized he had held.

Then the man on the ground raised his head, and turned toward Draco, panting, and breathed: "Draco, my boy, I am sorry to let you see me in such a state."

-Father.

Draco could not believe his eyes; he could not believe his ears. Maybe, maybe Snape did something to him, maybe he didn't hold his mental barrier as he thought he did, or it was all a bad joke…

Snape spoke amidst casting healing charms: "You can verify his identity using your patronus."

In so many sleepless nights that Draco had sent his patronus to find Father, and only receiving sad looks. But this time, Draco's snake patronus happily lept and jumped to the man on the ground.

Draco ran down the stairs regardless of the possible dangers. He just wanted to hug the man on the floor, and never to leave his side.

As Draco reached the bottom of the suitcase, Snape had finished casting spells, and shoved a red glass into the hand of the white-haired man on the ground. Snape swayed a bit, and then lent a hand to Father to help him up. "Hopefully, the next hour will be safe. I'll leave it to you and your son. Call me immediately if anything goes wrong."

Draco watched as Father grabbed Snape's hand and climbed up. It was strange to see Father in such a weakened state, and needing other's help to get up, like something perfect that had started to crack.

Before Draco could figure out anything to say, Father spoke first: "Draco, I died a year ago. Severus, my dearest friend and brother in all but blood, revived me five days ago. Since then, he has saved my life at least thirty-eight times. There is no word that I can use to express my gratitude toward him."

Snape stared at Father, as if being quite annoyed by Father's words, then shook his head and climbed up the stairs, murmuring: "Don't die in the next hour. I really need some sleep."

The moment Snape disappeared from the staircase and the suitcase door got closed, Father opened his arms, with some tears glistening in his eyes.

Draco knew this was the hint that he could abandon Malfoy demeanor now, in front of the very man who taught him how to behave like a Malfoy.

Draco threw himself into Father's arms and began sobbing.

Chapter 14: Interlude

3:53 pm, June 24th, 1993

Short Interlude, Draco Malfoy

Draco watched as the dark-haired man sitting on the other couch drank down a bottle of Invigoration Draught. Draco wasn't quite sure what he was supposed to feel toward Severus.

The Severus Snape that Draco knew didn't seem like a man that Father would be close to. All Father's close friends such as Mr. Macnair and Mr. Avery that Draco knew of were cunning and decent purebloods who could never stand a stain on their exquisite robes. Severus was cunning and powerful for sure, but he was a half-blood, his mother was a laughstock among purebloods, and he himself didn't respect any social etiquette, either - he didn't even clean his hair and robes properly. However, Father and Severus were indeed allies for many years, maybe it was because they both spoke Parseltongue so that they couldn't tell direct lies to each other.

And then, Severus REVIVED Father. Even in the tragic plays, people tried to resurrect lost lovers, not dead allies or friends. Draco could hardly describe his gratitude and shock toward Severus' great deed.

Today, Father told Draco that he suspected Severus was emotionally hungry, so if you treated him with true friendship and goodwill, that man would return your favor hundreds folds. Father had recognized life debts owned by House Malfoy toward Severus, and proclaimed Severus as his brother in all but blood. Draco was told that he should treat Severus so. Draco had no problem recognizing the life debts, but to treat the unkempt potioneer as a real uncle, that would still take some adjustment.

Then Father also told Draco that he had invited Severus to be his godfather. Draco was so astonished that he almost checked if Father was an imposter. Draco knew Father really believed in pureblood supremacy. How could Father possibly invited a half-blood to be a Malfoy godfather? Father quickly assured Draco that since he was going to reach his magical majority within the next week, Severus wouldn't have any legal power over Draco, but Severus would protect Draco with his life anyway.

-OK, that is definitely Father.

And there came this man sitting in front of Draco, freely offering information that would help Draco redeem Slytherin, even the lot that Draco had deemed as hopeless. "Miss Parkinson might not be sharp, nor kind, but the Parkinsons have a reputation to be obedient to their head of house. A young Mr. Parkinson will enter Hogwarts this September. I have seen the boy once or twice, he might not be beyond redemption. Miss Parkinson would probably follow the next Head of Parkinson House's suit with some nudge in the right direction."

Draco duly nodded, and listed the young Mr. Parkinson as one of the persons he needed to talk to in the beginning of next semester.

Maybe Draco had spent too much time with Harry and Hermione, he started to feel that the way Father tried to use Severus wasn't really fair for the black-haired man. If he were to become Draco's godfather, Draco needed to treat him fairly, and it was not exactly the way that Father considered fair.

-OK, Severus is keen on redeeming Slytherin as well, so maybe I should work our relationships up from here. And I do need to send him better robes, toothpaste, and shampoos. Hopefully, Severus won't murder his new godson for sending him shampoo, will he?

Just as Draco was pondering if he could cut down cost somewhere so that he could buy Severus a house elf that was ridiculously expensive these days, the door of the suitcase opened, and Harry stepped out.

Severus quickly stood up from his couch, and glanced at Father on the bottom of the suitcase. Draco also stood up, and Father seemed to be OK.

Severus then turned to Harry. "Mr. Potter, I need to talk to you in private as well. And in the meanwhile, I wonder if Narcissa could be here. She is a strong witch who is good at healing spells."

Draco looked at Harry expectantly, and some warmth toward Severus also rose from heart. Draco knew the time that his whole family were allowed to be together was quite limited, but he'd better not offend Harry by nagging. And Severus had just asked a difficult question that Draco wasn't sure how to ask.

Severus' request seemed to surprise Harry a bit, but the Boy-Who-Lived soon agreed to let Mother come here as well.

Chapter 17: Tests

5:32 pm, June 24th, 1993

Harry watched as Severus reapplied the charm that banned anyone from coming into the room, contemplating the tests yet to run.

In the meanwhile, Hermione seemed to be a little unsure about how to face the man who had humiliated her horribly in public, according to some grand plan designed by Dumbledore; yet helped her SPHEW cause secretly without anyone knowing about it. "Good afternoon, Professor Snape. How was your trip?"

Severus finished casting the spells, and turned around to face Harry and Hermione. "Miss Granger, my trip entailed a long story that Mr. Potter may prefer to explain to you in private. Before I leave you two for your discussion, I need to say that with Albus' order or not, I have not treated you fairly, and my actions have caused you great distress. One year ago, in my haste to pursue power beyond my own limit, I have neglected to apologize to you. I apologize to you now."

To be honest, Harry didn't quite expect that from the ex-Potions master.

- Is Severus doing this because he had become a better man? Or, is it because the man is ready to serve a benign Light Lord, so that he wants to repair his relationships with the Lord's most trusted advisor?

Hufflepuff preferred the first reason, while Slytherin argued that since Severus was a true Slytherin, it was probably the more cynical answer. Either way, this seemed to be a good thing if Harry needed Severus for his plots later.

Needless to say, Hermione stared at Severus in open shock. When she managed to speak, her voice was a little flustered. "I mean, err, Harry has told that you were the one who put notes under my pillow to help me fight bullies. I actually need to thank you for that. And, well, as for the other parts, I guess it's alright now since we all know why it happened."

Severus nodded, and pulled out a black suitcase from his pouch. "I will enter this suitcase and seal myself in it. Notify me when I am needed. I sspoke truth."

Severus smirked upon Hermione's gasp.

Before Severus put the black suitcase beside the grey one, Harry gave Hermione an explain-to-you-later look, and said, "Professor Snape, could you show your patronus to Hermione and me? Maybe we will be able to see something."

Severus' eyes flickered, then pulled out his wand. "Expecto Patronum."

A basketball-sized bright white ball jumped out of Severus' wand point. It was not nearly as bright as Harry's or Hermione's, but it is way brighter than a regular animal patronus. The white ball went in front of Hermione, and said in the ex-Potions master's smooth voice, "The sky is blue."

Hermione stared at Severus' patronus, then eyed Harry with a disapproving look.

Severus then offered, "The memory I need to use to fuel this patronus is quite peculiar. The first time I managed it, some of the memories couldn't even be counted as happy ones for most people. I needed to remember Draco's crying face, and my nausea upon seeing - Well, later I somehow have to include my grief upon hearing the deaths of people I cared about to use the charm. This is strange indeed."

Harry knew the reason, but he wasn't sure that he should tell Severus now. It was because Severus refused to accept the deaths of the ones he cared, and he wanted them to be alive. Severus needed to go one step higher, to want everyone to live forever and to absolutely refuse death to use the true patronus.

Anyway, Severus had passed one of Harry's tests.

Hermione looked at Severus with some admiration, then said. "Professor Snape, I think I know why, but I am not sure I can tell you."

"Mr. Potter said so as well, it seems I need to entangle this riddle myself." Severus' eyes centered on Hermione's sparkling fingernails. "I suppose I know some of the reasons that you could destroy several hundred dementors now."

Severus suddenly frowned, and his face became as white as plaster. "I don't know any magic that can end the unicorn power inside you, but I can't say such thing is impossible. Miss Granger, please be very careful not to lose it, otherwise the world will be in grave danger."

Hermione nodded in confusion.

Harry was a bit confused as well.

-Ending the power of unicorn that gives Hermione tremendous life power would definitely be bad, but how can that lead to world destruction?

"Well, I guess I need to be specific. There is some potion lore about the origin of Felix Felicis, the Liquid Luck potion. It is said that the reason that unicorn blood can sustain life for a while is that it is the strongest Felix Felicis, it will grant you so much luck that your body will heal itself against all odds and possibilities. But afterwards, the universe will work against you. From the Dark Lord's experience, I guess people cannot escape this side effect even if one changes into a new body." Severus said gravely. "And I would not suggest either of you take Felix Felicis unless absolutely necessary. Generations of potioneers had improved the potion to minimize the side effects, but I am not sure what the effect would be on Miss Granger. And in general, relying too much on Felix Felicis invariably leads to disastrous results."

Now Harry began to understand why most dying people didn't drink unicorn blood, and why people said anyone who drank the blood could only live "a cursed life, a half life". Unicorn blood and the Liquid Luck potion seemed to have some unexplained results on which timeline the Universe chose amongst all the possible timelines, but the Universe fought back hard. In a word, after drinking unicorn blood, if you wanted heads in a gamble of flipping coins, you would get all heads; but afterward, it would be all tails.

Harry had wondered how he came out to defeat Lord Voldemort against all odds, and why the smart enemy suddenly fell into the literary trap of a stupid talking villain, now Harry saw it. The Universe was working against Voldemort. Voldemort might have thought changing into a new body would end the side effect, but obviously it was not the case.

Harry imagined what he would do on the verge of death before he knew the ritual and the power of the Stone, and shuddered. Harry would do exactly the same thing Voldemort did, drank unicorn blood, and the world would be destroyed in any of the previous world-ending incidences. On the other hand, the reason that the world had not ended in the previous incidences, might exactly be that Hermione, who was blessed with all the luck of the Universe for the time being, was standing beside Harry.

Severus pondered, sighed, and retrieved two bottles of golden liquid from his pouch. "I brewed these Felix Felicis myself, much better than the things you can buy in the market. The side effect is minimized to the best of my abilities. If you two absolutely need luck, use these. I will give Draco one bottle and give him the same instructions as well. I sspoke truth. Potionss were for m-mysself, no trick."

Upon hearing the "no trick" statement, Harry knew Severus had realized he was being tested, but tests still needed to be run.

As Harry and Hermione each took a bottle of Liquid Luck from Severus, Harry said, "Professor Snape, thank you so much for your advice and the potion. Do you know any other side effects of anything else?"

"For trolls, I only know that they are really stupid and violent, much easier to deal with than the side effects of unicorn blood." Severus then hesitated a little, and hissed. "Hor-horcruxess ssaid to be ominouss for ov… offsssp-ringss, or kids born with b-bad luck, not ssure if true."

Harry didn't dare to look at Hermione. He didn't trust his occlumency barrier could hide the horror and the guilt in him.

-No, no, no!

As of the past several months, Harry began to have some romantic thoughts on Hermione. But if what Severus heard was true, Hermione should never have kids, and the birth of her child - THEIR child - might tilt the world towards destruction.

"I do not know anyone elsse … m-made hor-horcruxess for another, v-while other not know-v-wing, though." Severus hissed more.

Harry was a little bit assured, but the stone on his heart was still quite heavy.

-OK, one reason NOT to make horcruxes for everyone with sacrifices of blank-brained clones. And this explains why dark wizards like Lucius may choose not to make horcruxes. A calculated cold-blooded murderer as Lucius is, he probably loves Draco more than his own life. As for Voldemort, kids are definitely not one of his concerns, or he simply didn't believe legends not to his taste. Or, maybe people fabricated this lore so that dark wizards like Lucius would not make horcruxes and live forever.

Severus stopped, then his hisses somehow became more grave. "I do not know effectss of v-unicorn blood on ts-childbirth, either."

Hermione saw Harry's blank face upon hearing the hisses, and asked carefully. "Am I to know?"

Severus and Harry looked at each other. Harry's voice wavered a bit as he answered. "I need to think about it."

"OK." Hermione accepted without hesitation.

Harry's heart sank further.

-It may not even be true. Just run your next test.

"Professor Snape, thank you so much. I will talk with Hermione for a while, and I will call you by patronus afterwards." Harry said politely, and Severus descended down his black suitcase.

After the door of the suitcase was closed, Hermione started to cast privacy spells, and then asked. "Harry, what is all that about?"

"Hmm, let's wait for a while to let Professor Snape finish his spells inside his suitcase, and let me finish mine." Ten spells later, Harry moved towards his couch. "In the meanwhile, did you bring the books I asked for?"

Hermione drew out several huge books, including Comprehensive Wizarding Genealogy, Pure-Blood Directory, and Distinguished Surnames in History, and put them onto the table in front of Harry's couch. "Why do need those books?" Hermione asked with a tone of suspicion.

"Just checking." Harry started to flip through the pages, and easily found Salazar Slytherin's name from Comprehensive Wizarding Genealogy. He saw, as sort of expected, one of Salazar's granddaughters married Armand Malfoy's son, Draco Malfoy I. And about fifty years later, a Malfoy girl descended from the first Draco got married with an wizard named "Arthur the Weasel", who was the founder of the Weasley family. Harry knew he could stop looking there, because there were so many Weasleys in wizarding Britain that they were virtually related to every family.

-Well, it seems most wizards in Britain are descendants of Salazar Slytherin anyway. This makes a lot of sense for a small society like this, that everyone is basically related to everyone. I am a third cousin of Narcissa and Bellatrix; and there was a famous potioneer with the lastname of Dagworth-Granger in the seventeenth or eighteenth century, Hermione might be related to him. Maybe it was only the Gaunt family that kept inbreeding, so only all the Gaunts were known to speak Parseltongue, and Salazar's magic was just thinned out in other families. The same way as veela-human hybrids do. The half-veelas look more veela than human, but quarter-veelas look more human, and so on. And Professor Flitwick, who has distant goblin ancestry, is mostly human except his height and squeaky voice. This also explains why Lucius can speak much better Parseltongue than Severus. Too bad that not every wizard in the world is a descendant of Salazar.

-And that, is probably why Salazar's monster is said to be able to rid muggleborns from Hogwarts, since the muggleborns probably can't learn Parseltongue, therefore can't be taught by the most knowledgeable teacher in Hogwarts.

"What are you checking?" Hermione read Comprehensive Wizarding Genealogy upside-down, and formed a quick guess. "You thought Professor Snape is an heir of Slytherin?"

"Well, virtually most wizards in Britain are, and a lot more in Europe and the western world, I guess." Harry quickly flipped through the long list of names of the Weasley family, and pointed to the beginning, "See, the founder of the Weasley family got married with one of Salazar's great-great granddaughters, so it is easy to guess from there."

"Then why there aren't that many known Parselmouths?" Hermione asked.

"I guess it may take quite some learning for most wizards, except the extreme inbreeding Gaunt family. Professor Snape said Professor Dumbledore can speak it as well. I have always wondered why Dumbledore trusted Severus Snape, it all makes sense now." Harry answered.

"OK, should I learn Parseltongue, then?" Hermione quickly asked, eagerness in her eyes. "Or perhaps I am not a descendent of Slytherin. I guess maybe Draco should as well."

"You can learn if you want to, we just need to dig your family history a bit. And I think Draco will learn it from his new godfather and others anyway." Harry said to his wide-eyed friend. "Yeah, as you may have guessed, Professor Snape is going to be Draco's godfather, and would you be one of the witnesses for the legal process?"

Hermione nodded, confusion in her eyes. "Of course. But why didn't they do it one year ago, after, you know?"

"Well, that's quite related to what I am about to tell you." Harry sat down on his couch. "Before that, I just have one more test to run. Hermione, could you use your patronus to find the Dark Lord, and, say, Nott Sr., then Bellatrix Black, and tell them the good news that when we bring them back, we will make them better people."

Hermione looked at Harry with suspicion. "You know the Dark Lord is transfigured, and Nott Sr. is dead, right? But anyway, Expecto Patronum."

Hermione's bright patronus in the form of a girl jumped out from her wand point. The girl first stood there, looking really confused, then only looked sadly at Hermione, and finally, the patronus wandered around the room aimlessly as if not knowing where to go.

"OK, exactly the same result as I got a moment ago." Harry had an impulse to reach for his Comed-Tea, and suppressed it. "Before I can tell you what all this means, there's something I need to tell you, so that I can finish the story without giggling or laughing until you knock me down and bring me to St. Mungo's."

Hermione composed herself. "Say it, Harry."

"Professor Snape is a bat animagus."

Both Harry and Hermione fell into hysterical laughter.

"Oh, no, Harry, I - I am such a terrible person." Hermione giggled helplessly, and wiped her tears, "I shouldn't have laughed at him."

Harry was wiping laughing tears as well, but some of the tears may have come from another source.

The Next Chapter will be uploaded at 6 pm (EDT), 04/13/2015

Chapter 18: Answers

5:57 pm, June 24th, 1993

Third Private Meeting, Hermione, Answers

After Hermione's laughter finally dwindled down to giggles, Harry wiped his eyes dry, "Five days ago, Professor Snape revived Lucius Malfoy using the same ritual the Dark Lord used to revive you. Or, at least, both Severus Snape and Lucius Malfoy seriously believe this narrative, as verified by Parseltongue. I've got one more test that we can run a few hours later, but my current test results seemed to confirm at least part of the story."

Hermione gaped at Harry's statement.

Harry went on to recount the story Severus told him about that night, Severus' theory on revival, and about the revival of Lucius. After finishing the story, Harry began to explain the tests he did. "First, I asked Professor Snape to show his patronus. Since you were able to resist the Dark Lord's temptations, I thought you would be a good observer for this test. It seems that Professor Snape knows part of the secrets in the true patronus charm, mostly the part pointed out by Voldemort plus some of his own deductions. Secondly, I asked him if he knew anything else that could go wrong. It appears that Professor Snape knows that your ability to heal came from an unicorn and a troll. The unicorn part is pretty obvious just from your look, but not the troll part. The knowledge about the troll and the true patronus can't come from Lucius, who only came to the graveyard later."

-And Severus knows about the horcrux as well.

"So there is a high probability that Professor Snape was indeed there, observing the whole scene, though the Time barrier set up by the Dark Lord, or something else, prevented him from coming near or doing anything. And later that night, when he had every opportunity to take the true Stone and run away, he returned everything to me, and only took the duplicates of the Stone and the instruction manual." Harry showed Hermione the dull-looking red glass. "We can test to see if this duplicate can indeed extend transfiguration on a small item longer for a limited time in a few hours, but I guess we already got some conclusions. Correct me if I made any mistakes in my reasoning, I think we proved that Professor Snape did observe the scene, and though he is maybe a little bit shrewd, he is a good person deep down, or, at least he is someone who can resist great temptation."

Hermione thought for a while, and nodded.

"And about the test I let you run with your patronus, well, I have tested all the supposedly dead Death Eaters a few days after that night, just to check if they are really dead. It appeared that the transfigured Dark Lord confused my patronus; the dead ones made the patronus looked sad; and Bellatrix, who was on the run and might have some anti-patronus charm on herself, made my patronus wandered around aimlessly. One year ago, Lucius appeared to be dead-dead instead of transfigured-horcrux-dead to my patronus, or so it seemed at that time. I am sure Moody used other methods to check on his own as well. Therefore, Lucius was quite likely to be dead one year ago, or until Moody last checked." Harry reasoned. "Now, it is possible that Professor Snape figured out how to revive someone with well-preserved heads from the Dark Lord's instruction manual, and from the things he heard. Since he only had an inferior duplicate Stone, he couldn't stabilize Lucius' form, so they had to come to us."

Hermione blinked, and asked, "Or?"

"Or, Lucius had an improved version of horcrux or something alike, and Professor Snape revived him from there. These two modified each other's memories afterwards, or they had someone else do it, so both of them could truly believe what they said in Parseltongue." Harry said slowly, "But I don't really see the point for Professor Snape to lie about the revival process. I can go and ask Professor Snape to revive another Death Eater that he said he preserved, and verify if he could do it. Moody can check the altar Professor Snape used and everything related. So that's one of the reasons why I chose to believe Professor Snape."

Harry's inner critic timely offered, it is also because we want to revive mother and father and everyone else, therefore we wanted to believe him. For what was worse, we even wanted to believe his hair theory, which was obviously ridiculous. We should be sentenced in Rationality Prison for eternity for wanting to believe something like that after all this time.

Hermione pondered the question for a while. "Well, I can't offer any good reason for Professor Snape to lie about the revival, either. I am sure Moody can propose some ideas. And you talked with Lucius Malfoy as well?"

Harry nodded. "Yes, the whole conversation between Lucius and I was in Parseltongue. And here is the strange thing, Lucius Malfoy practically told me that memory charms could fool Parseltongue, but the effects of memory charms might be different from real events. Lucius told me that his first possible kill was when his tutor memory charmed him into believing a captured muggle killed his mother, so that he could hate the muggle enough to use the killing curse. He wasn't even sure the entire thing happened, and he still felt it extremely difficult to cast the killing curse in his first Death Eater raid under Bellatrix's wand point."

- And it is very hard to decide if Lucius was really being cooperative, or if he was playing the game one level higher than I am.

"He also defended himself in Parseltongue, saying that he didn't kill as many as people say he did, while he just told me that even Parseltongue could be fooled by memory charms." Harry sighed.

"So as to create plausible deniability?" Hermione asked.

"Or Lucius was offering truth to the best of his knowledge. I admit that I am confused. We need to draw a chart for this." Harry reached into his pouch. "Paper and pencil. First, let's have the variables and assign possibilities. I assume Lucius doesn't want the world to come to its end, let that be 99.9%. The probability that Lucius loves Draco is, 95%, maybe? Or he is an amazing actor, 5%. The probability that he wants to secure Draco's position, or promote him, hmm, let's say 90% in total, and 10% for he wants power for himself. Within the first category, Lucius may want to alienate us so that Draco can be number two -"

-Ha, if Lucius knew Voldemort made a horcrux for Hermione from Severus, he was probably the one who told Severus there was a rumor about horcruxes might be ominous for offsprings, or he did it by memory charms to let Severus think he heard it somewhere else. He expected Severus to tell me this, so I would be careful not to have kids with Hermione, and I would try to stop Hermione from having kids until everything got settled out. He might think that's a way that he can keep Hermione and I apart. Hmm, I can certainly verify if there is indeed a rumor and when the rumor came out by myself.

Harry's inner critics interjected. Are you sure you are not in the wishful thinking mode again? You wanted to believe horcruxes are OK to have, as long as you don't kill others for it yourself. Plus, it wasn't that likely for Severus to tell Lucius the details of that night. Lucius had to guess about the details of the ritual, remember? And don't forget the unknown effect of unicorn blood on childbirth.

Hermione also obtained a pencil from her pouch, and started to help drawing a Bayesian chart while Harry recounted some of the things Lucius said in their conversation.

Just as Harry began to explain his discussion with Lucius on prison sentence, Hermione put down her pencil, and looked at Harry in the eyes. "Harry, I have a question. I understand that Lucius and you needed to agree on a plausible story and so on, and I am happy that he will be tried as himself. However, why did Lucius Malfoy confess his sins and negotiate his prison sentence with you? Instead of Madam Bones or anyone in the Department of Law Enforcement? Plea bargains should be negotiated with prosecutors, Harry. And determining the years to be served in prison by a Death Eater is not a war decision, so it should undergo the due legal process."

"Ahh… " Harry opened his mouth.

Harry didn't think of that. Apparently, nor did Lucius, nor Severus, nor Draco. Maybe this was the way how things were always done in the wizarding world, where people with real powers negotiate deals behind closed doors. Lucius successfully deduced - or Draco just told him - that Harry was behind Madam Bones. Guessing out this part wasn't hard after all. Therefore, Lucius wanted to reach a deal directly with Harry.

"Harry, this scares me sometimes, you know." Hermione said in a flat tone.

"But - well, OK, you're right." Harry admitted reluctantly. "But I don't think I could let Lucius tell Madam Bones his reason for shorter imprisonment. Lucius was the binder for the Vow, I can't let Madam Bones know about the Vow, or the Prophecy that I may destroy the world. Even if only 0.01% of the people potentially saved by the Vow can be attributed to Lucius, he still saved 2.4 million people."

Hermione retorted. "But you said Lucius was forced by Voldemort to do it, he didn't volunteer. And Lucius Malfoy wanted to put me in Azkaban, Harry. Azkaban with dementors!"

"That's true, but -" Now Harry's inner selves were conflicting between his care for Hermione and that for Draco. He sighed. "As I told you, the Dark Lord thought my game with Draco might lead to Lucius' moves against me, so he wanted to remove Lucius from the gameboard and alienate Draco from Lucius. The Dark Lord framed you in the attempted murder of Draco, called for the Azkaban sentence, and planned to present iron-clad evidences saying that Lucius did it to exile or imprison Lucius. Lucius, well, I guess he was evil enough to fall into the Dark Lord's trap, but some fathers who were not as evil as Lucius might also fall into the same trap. And after the Dark Lord murdered you, with some tricks from my part, Lucius reached a deal with me, became an ally, and carried out his part of the deal pretty well as far as I know. I guess that was part of the reason why the Dark Lord chose Lucius as the binder. So, at least, I am partially responsible for Lucius becoming the binder, and Lucius did try to do some good things before he died."

"You still know Lucius is evil, and you respect law and justice, right?" Hermione asked.

"I do. I just -" Harry stuttered.

-I just don't want to hurt Draco anymore. Draco almost lost his father when Voldemort tried to frame Lucius for the attempted murder, because I played my little games with Draco; then Draco did lose his father, because I killed Lucius; and now, for the third time…

"Hermione, there is," Harry gulped, "Draco. You know what the last year was like for him. I feel like - I don't want Draco to lose his father again, and I also need to make sure justice is served."

Hermione looked at Harry in the eyes, and argued reasonably. "That's exactly why you shouldn't be the judge here, Harry. I would understand if you want to treat Lucius Malfoy as the father of a friend, help him get lawyers, and you can testify in front of Madam Bones or the Wizengamot that what he said in Parseltongue is known to himself to be true. You should hand the legal process to professionals, so that you can be the friend who will help Draco to make sure that his father will get a fair trial. Just don't use your Boy-Who-Lived and Line of Merlin Unbroken power to force any leniency."

-Ahh…

That, that didn't occur to Harry, either. All of a sudden, the Boy-Who-Lived's face brightened up a bit, and his voice lighter, "Hermione, you are right. I didn't think of it. Yeah, after due legal processes, I can sort of let Madam Bones consider some reason to reduce Lucius' term, say, his escape and lost of magic had contributed a little bit in the prevention of world destruction by the Dark Lord's remnant."

Hermione gave Harry a disapproving look.

"Or, I will say that it was something that she is not to know, but Lucius was forced to sacrifice much of his magic to save quite a number of people, which is true as well." Harry thought of another reason.

"By the way, maybe we should ask Madam Bones to excuse herself from this case, because she has a conflict of interest, since her brother's whole family were murdered by Lucius." Hermione's brows frowned a bit. "Who in the Department of Law Enforcement doesn't have a conflict of interest? It's really hard to find someone considering Lucius' criminal history."

Harry felt a huge burden had been taken off from his shoulder, now he could defend Lucius as he liked. "I haven't tell you this part yet. Lucius said that Karkaroff led the raid on Madam Bones' brother's family, Bellatrix led the one on Monroe family, and he said he wasn't in either of those. He denied all sex-related crimes as well."

"What? Why? Are you sure he didn't memory charm himself or have someone else do it?" Hermione asked.

"I'm not sure," Harry answered. "But he did offer a very good explanation, sort of. Remember that I told you the Dark Lord intentionally made his enemies more worthy? I guess the slaughter of the Bones family that only left Madam Bones and Susan unscathed was one such event, where the Dark Lord wanted to have a cunning and powerful witch who hated him enough. When Lucius was given such an assignment, Lucius just refused to create a powerful enemy like that, and managed to weasel out. Well, if my guesses are correct, few of Lucius' victims have any powerful family members left alive to pursue justice."

Hermione paused and frowned. "That explanation does make some sense, but it somehow scares me more than the ruthless random killings people say he did."

-No, it isn't. A sane and cunning enemy like Lucius tries to control the damage, or not to cause damage unless necessary; while a crazy or stupid one may be easy to defeat, but you have no idea what they might do. The evil and sane dark wizards like Voldemort and Lucius would try to prevent world destruction; a stupid or negligent villain, or "hero" for that matter, may not be able to suppress their curiosity, and just press the "Do Not Press, otherwise World Will End" button anyway.

Harry sighed. "Hermione, maybe I have too high a standard, sometimes, I just hoped all our enemies, or all people, are half as sane as the Dark Lord, or even half as cunning as Lucius. Just think of this, if the whole revival thing goes public, and it is indeed as easy as Professor Snape originally thought, that one hair is enough, what would happen? I bet some negligent idiots will just try dangerous things that they would not usually try, and cause great damage to themselves and to the world. Remember what happened when we made the Stone available to everyone? We set up a queue system where people who wants to be younger and looks better can sign up on it, and the Hospital will do whatever they like when it is their turn and when the Stone is not in need for real lethal conditions. However, within less than one month, we saw an influx of witches and wizards who conducted free transfiguration on themselves, or did something equally stupid to themselves, so that they could have a real lethal condition that needed to be fixed by the Stone, and to have the nose they liked, or teeth they preferred at the same time. Several idiots did this multiple times, because they wanted to try different noses, or skin tones, or something like that. Several people died before they could get to the Hospital. They wouldn't die if they just waited in the queue and let professionals do it, or if they didn't know the Stone existed. When the news that high officials from all over the world are working on a law to imprison the idiots who did stupid things to themselves multiple times, the number of people in emergency just increased, because they wanted to get better looks before the law was passed. That's how stupid and reckless people can be if they think they have some sort of safenet, even when they still know that they can really die. Think what would happen when they know a single hair can revive them."

Hermione paused to think, and shuddered.

The world may not be ended by some smart villains, just by some reckless idiots, or by some arrogant heroes like us. All parts of Harry agreed on this particular topic. We need to rationalize the mind of everyone before we make revival publically available.

"So anyway, we need to figure out a way to let people learn to be rational and careful, whilst not destroying the world in the teaching process." Harry sighed again.

Hermione nodded in agreement.

"Hermione, there is one more thing about Lucius that I need your opinion." Then Harry explained how Lucius would be quite useful in the dealing of international politics, and how Lucius' mind could be used to predict other dark wizards' movements. "The international politics stuff, I may be able to figure it out within a few years, the real problem is how to predict the thoughts of dark wizards. Dumbledore had difficulty in understanding Voldemort, Moody said he had difficulty predicting Lucius, Snape hadn't thought of the danger of the Stone and the revival ritual before Lucius pointed out to him, and I need to go into my dark side to predict Voldemort's moves. Oh, well, maybe I am only able to predict sane or semi-sane dark wizards. Two years ago, when I just met Draco, catering to fools were part of his instincts; while I was unable to lower my standard to do that, and maybe that's still who I am. So my guesses for Lucius Malfoy is that, he has a better understanding of the dark wizards' minds and the stupidity and other characteristic fallacies of common people. I wonder if we can use Lucius for these purposes."

Hermione fell into silence. Harry knew Hermione was in the same type of dilemma as he was. Lucius Malfoy was a calculating dark wizard and cold-blooded murderer himself, and was an expert in the exploitation of common people's stupidity, negligence, fear, greediness and other human flaws by generations of practise. These might be quite handy in the time being. However, such abilities of Lucius were objectionable in Hermione and Harry's moral systems, and both of them wanted to rid such things from human nature in the future. Plus, the trustworthiness of Lucius was a big pending question.

After a while, Hermione said with a frown. "Let's finish the Bayesian chart first, then we will have some standards to estimate how trustworthy Lucius is. We will figure out some ways to verify our prediction, and go from there." Hermione continued drawing on the paper, and said. "OK, I can think of one big question now: did Lucius modify his memory about the number of murders he committed? Professor Snape was a Death Eater, and he might know something about the murders Lucius denied, unless his memory was modified as well. Let's have Professor Snape on the chart as well."

-Well, Karkaroff is probably not that reliable as a witness, neither is Severus. The majority of Death Eaters in Nurmengard hardly remember the birthday of their kids. Letting Severus revive Quirrell might be a solution, but that will create more problems than solving them. And Bellatrix Black, I wonder how to catch her.

Then a horrible idea came to Harry.

-What would Voldemort/Harry do after being trapped by horcruxes hidden in obscure places?A cunning man as Voldemort was, he might not rely on one plan to work. Linking his Version 2.0 horcrux system to the Resurrection Stone, and put some horcruxes in more obvious places, might not be his only improvements. He might entrust some of his horcruxes to Bellatrix as well. Since Voldemort is not dead, Version 2.0 horcruxes do not work now, but the Version 1.0 horcruxes do.

-What order would Voldemort/Harry give to Bellatrix?

-Guard my items well and hide yourself well while I return to my true body. If a certain item is activated, physically touch it, put your heart and soul to it. Otherwise, wait for a certain amount of time, if you are not contacted, trigger another set of items. Say, a Version 1.0 horcrux made just before I tried my hands on the Stone. And little Bella, I also have some knowledge that I need to temporarily store in your mind, but you are not to use them or think of them except to pass them back on to me. Or simply, just guard my pet snake really well, and don't look at it in the eyes.

"Harry, what's your idea for testing Lucius' trustworthiness? You are awfully quiet." Hermione asked while drawing a line between "Snape modified Lucius' memory" and "Snape lied about resurrection ritual".

Harry's voice was unsteady as he said the sentences. "A ticking bomb of a lesser version of Voldemort returning. Once I began to throw away some of my previous assumptions, I didn't even need to sink into my dark side to see it. Voldemort might have entrusted some of his horcruxes to Bellatrix, and gave her an order when to trigger them unless contacted. One year seems to be a good waiting period to me. We need to find Bellatrix Black, very soon."

Hermione put down her pencil, hand shaking a little. "Harry, are you 99% sure that neither Lucius nor Professor Snape wants You-Know-Who back? If so, we should ask them to think as hard as possible on how to find Bellatrix Black."

Harry looked at Hermione sadly. "Yes, we should. I will also ask Moody and Madam Bones, and I will sink into my dark side as well. Wake me up if I don't come back in fifteen minutes."

Then, under the watchful eyes of his most trusted female companion, the Boy-Who-Lived sank fully into his dark side, wondering where Voldemort's most devoted female follower would be.

The next chapter will be up at 6 pm (EDT), 04/15/2015

Chapter 20: The Faithful Servent

6:47 pm, June 27th, 1993

Bellatrix Black was shaking all over herself when she trigger the portkey.

-Oh, Merlin, my Lord must be so displeased. Little Bella has lost the track of time. Little Bella is so late.

A month or so after her Lord retrieved her from Azkaban, Bellatrix couldn't quite remember the date back then, the snake animagus that had accompanied her Lord came to the secret hiding place. He said her Lord might need little Bella's left arm for a ritual to return to his true body. Bellatrix was so happy that she was again useful for her Lord, and she cut off her left arm without any hesitation. Actually, she didn't even feel any pain, because her Lord also ordered the snake animagus to move her Dark Mark to her breast, right above where her heart was. With each heartbeat, Bellatrix felt her Lord was with her. And her Lord also said that she should practice magic as hard as she could, and he might need her skills later as well.

Bellatrix was beyond herself as she thought of the possibility that her Lord might need her skills someday. She obeyed all the orders from the healer woman Crystal Camblebunker, who was sent to heal her by her Lord, so that she could be stronger when the time came. And Bellatrix practiced magic as hard as she could.

Even within her disoriented and fragmented memories, Bellatrix could still clearly remember that special date, June 13th, 1992. That morning, the snake animagus man, Jeremy Jaffe, came again. This time, that man ordered her healer to go with him, and gave Bellatrix some very important missions. Bellatrix was given a pouch and a set of instructions that she could only look at if her Dark Mark was not dark again within the next twenty-four hours.

Since Jeremy Jaffe and her healer left, Bellatrix had been watching her Dark Mark the whole day. The sun rose to its full height, and fell. The Dark Mark did not change. The moon rose, and rose. As the moon got to around its highest point, the Dark Mark suddenly turned black. Bellatrix almost couldn't believe her own eyes.

-My Lord is back! He is back! In his true body!

Bellatrix cried with happiness and joy, she danced under the moon, all the time watching her beautiful Dark Mark jumping up and down on her breast. She wanted to shoot a Morsmordre to the sky to tell the world that her Lord was back, but she was previously instructed to lay low by her Lord, so she hid her joy to herself.

However, Bellatrix's joy didn't last long. Her Mark suddenly flared up, as if burning through her soul and entire body.

-Oh, my Lord must be so angry at useless Little Bella. Does he want me to Crucio myself?

Just as Bellatrix was about to Crucio herself, some memory that she tried to forget emerged: that horrible Halloween night. All of a sudden, her Lord disappeared without a trace or message.

-No, Bella, you can't think that. It must be…

The pain above her heart subdued, and the color of the Dark Mark receded to light grey.

Bellatrix wanted to Crucio someone, she wanted to Crucio herself. She couldn't believe this, she couldn't accept this!

It was only that her Lord's order this morning that kept Bellatrix from running out to look for her Lord.

-Maybe, maybe my Lord will come back again. He told Little Bella to wait for twenty-four hours.

Bellatrix waited, and waited.

Tears ran dry. Wails became inaudible whispers.

The twenty-four hour mark passed. Her Dark Mark was still grey.

With trembling hands, Bellatrix opened the pouch she got one day ago. In the pouch, there was a note written in her Lord's handwriting, and several twigs. On that note, Bellatrix was instructed to trigger the portkey in the shape of green twig in her pouch in one year's time if she was not instructed otherwise. She should remain in the current place unless it was found by someone, in which case Bellatrix was not to fight. Instead, she should trigger a random twigs in any other color but green, and hide there instead. Food, water and potions for one year's use had been prepared for her in all locations. And Bellatrix should also read the Daily Prophet delivered to her hiding place, so she could hide herself better in case all locations had been found by someone.

Bellatrix did as she was instructed. She ate food, drank potions, and read the Daily Prophet that somehow appeared at her doorstep every morning without an owl.

However, without the healer woman, Bellatrix had began to lose the track of time, or even herself. She sometimes forgot to drink her potions in time, and ended up drank multiple bottles at the same time when she remembered, but that only seemed to make things worse.

Bellatrix tried to read the Daily Prophet every day, but she began to lose the grasps on the meanings of the words. Bellatrix remembered the paper had run long stories on how her Lord attempted to gain omnipotence by the sacrifice of all Death Eaters, how the mudblood girl - Granger or something - spoiled the whole plan, and how David Monroe might also be involved. Bellatrix didn't believe a single word in it. How could her Lord be defeated by a mudblood girl, or the David Monroe guy who had only created some minor troubles for her Lord?

There was also something else on the Daily Prophet that had caught Bellatrix's attention. It was about the return of Narcissa. Bellatrix didn't have much memory of her youngest sister, except the anguish and anger she felt when she heard Narcissa was burnt alive in her own bedroom. She wanted to kill Dumbledore for it, she wanted to kill the useless ponce Lucius Malfoy for it, but her Lord had forbidden all revenges. Bellatrix couldn't remember much beyond that, which meant other memories about Narcissa were happy ones. Now, all Bellatrix had was the newspaper, where a beautiful woman smiled beside a blond boy whose face looked too much a resemblance of his useless and treacherous father.

On a later paper, the sister that Bellatrix didn't really remember she had was caught to meet Lesath Lestrange in Mary's Place. And that was a name that Bellatrix didn't quite remember, either. Bellatrix remembered the horror and disgust she felt when she knew she was impregnated by either one of the Lestrange brothers, how she wanted to get rid of the thing in her belly, and how she was ordered by her Lord to give birth to the baby. Narcissa had hugged her, brought her things when she was pregnant, and cried, maybe? Oh, she remembered. She had berated Narcissa for her weakness, because if her Lord wanted her to have the baby, Little Bella was going to do that, and it was not Narcissa's place to insinuate that Little Bella should at least get married. As for the childbirth, and whatever happened around the child afterwards, Bellatrix couldn't recall. So there might be some happy memories there.

And there were all that news on the Stone, and the Hospital. They said that the mudblood girl killed all the dementors in Azkaban, and a hospital with some fancy name, which everyone just call it the Hospital, was built there. The healing power of the Stone was used to heal everyone from old age and disease. The place of desperation now became a place of hope and life. But there were rumors that the real location of the Hospital was not in Azkaban, but in Hogwarts, or in a sealed chamber in the Department of Mysteries set up by Merlin himself, or in some other secret locations, protected by some ancient wards.

Bellatrix knew her Lord would want that Stone, but her was ordered to wait. So she waited, and waited.

Bellatrix practiced magic while waiting, she planned her revenge while waiting, she ate and drank while waiting, and she downed the potions while waiting.

The problem was, Bellatrix began to lose the track of time and the track of herself while waiting. She had slept for days after she drank too much potion in one dose. She had woken up in odd places in the ward set up by her Lord, like in a corner of the yard, on the dining table, or on the rooftop.

When Bellatrix woke up this time amidst cockroaches and plastic wrappings of muggle food this time, she was horrified to find out that she had drank all the potions her Lord left her, and she had missed the one year mark!

Bellatrix trembled all over herself when she fumbled to find the pouch, and broke the green twig.

A hook grabbed Bellatrix's navel point, and the world swirled.

Bellatrix steadied herself, and looked at the surroundings. She was inside some cavern dimly lit by eerie green light, and the place she stood was a small island in the middle of a great black lake. Something on the bottom of the lake seemed to be unsettled by the sound of Bellatrix's landing, and began to gather.

However, those were not Bellatrix's concerns. No matter it was Heaven or Hell, Little Bella would just do her Lord's bidding. Her eyes were instantly attracted by a green pouch a few feet away from her. Bellatrix grabbed the pouch, and took out a note. The note in her Lord's handsome writing said:

"My Dear Bella,

Those who desire light will be engulfed by it.

Drink your final dose of potion in the pouch, then obliviate yourself of all your memories except that you will take a cup out from the pouch afterwards.

-L.V."

Bellatrix was quite happy to receive a new order from her Lord, but then she found her Lord ordered her to obviate herself of all her memories.

-Oh, my Lord has no use of Little Bella's memory anymore. But Little Bella will do as instructed.

Bellatrix called "potion", and a bottle of grey potion jumped into her hand. She drank down the bitter content in one gulp, then pointed her wand toward herself.

Bellatrix inhaled, exhaled, and thought of the vague faces of her youngest sister and her son for the last time.

"Obliviate."

The next chapter will be published at 6 pm (EDT), 04/19/2015.

Chapter 24: The Search, Pt II, Growing Up

7:06 am, June 28th, 1993

Severus' patronus woke everyone up in a jolt. In the ex-Head of Slytherin's smooth voice, the bright ball said, "I am still doing the headcount, but I am sure that quite a number of snakes went missing, especially the more powerful and venomous ones."

Harry rubbed his eyes, climbing up from his transfigured camp bed, and felt somewhat relieved: whoever the enemy is, he or she still needs more snakes to complete his or her mission, and the enemy or the enemy's paw was still in Hogwarts until the last several hours.

As Madam Bones sent out her patronus with a relieved smile, Harry thought of a certain powerful and venomous Blue Krait who was more intelligent and who might be able to provide more information than snakes with tracking spells. The problem was, Harry wasn't sure how Draco would take this.

Oh, haven't we done with useless qualms now? Remember the disastrous results of our other ethical qualms? Slytherin sneered. Just threaten the dementors properly, and dispatch them to prey on Voldemort the moment Lucius sends a mental call to the dementors. Do your multiplications and Imagine how much safer the world would be if this plan were successful.

But we don't want Draco to lose his father again. Hufflepuff said in a small voice. Especially, if the enemy is indeed Voldemort/Bellatrix, it is equal to handing "enemy's blood" to them.

We can let Lucius drink some interesting potions before we let him search the pipelines. Mad-Eye may know some. Slytherin said amidst horrified looks from all his other parts. Or, just a cube of ice transfigured from a liter of frozen sulfuric acid that due to last only forty-eight hours. This way, if Voldemort uses Lucius' blood to revive, we will see some quite interesting effects. And if Lucius comes back before that, the Stone can make sure that he wouldn't be hurt. Plus, we can make sure that Lucius wouldn't try to run away.

What would happen if Lucius was captured? Hufflepuff screamed at the top of his lungs. Lucius wouldn't have any brain left this time!

Remember that Dumbledore had sent our parents to die? It's probably the time for us to learn the same. Slytherin ignored the screams, and calmly suggested. We can revive Lucius after we figure out how to tear apart Reality and Time, right?

Harry didn't dare to look at Draco, whose face was turning whiter by the seconds.

A few seconds later, after Madam Bones signed some documents handed to her through the Floo, Mad-Eye Moody appeared in the fireplace with Lucius in full-body magical restraints.

Apparently, the old auror had made the difficult decision for Harry, again.

Lord Malfoy was allowed with his expensive and elegant robes, his hands were well manicured, and his long white mane was well groomed, for he was still Lord of a Noble and Most Ancient house, and he was not yet convicted. However, the unnatural paleness in his looks indicated something had already been taken care of.

Mad-Eye's lips twisted into a vicious smile, "Lucius has kindly offered to lead the search for the missing snakes. Haven't you, Lord Malfoy?"

Draco jumped up from his transfigured camp bed, reaching for his snake-headed wand, and only to be stopped by his father's stern stares. "Draco, the Department of Law Enforcement has agreed to drop some of the most baseless charges, and I might be able to have home visits for good behavior." Lucius' voice became a little softer. "Moreover, I am happy that I would be in your Adult Ceremony and to watch you become the next Lord Malfoy."

Then Lucius nodded to Madam Bones, "Madam Bones, would you please call for my wife Narcissa and Draco's godfather Severus here? The ceremony will be brief."

Harry could tell that Draco was fighting back his tears. Then, the blond boy began to quickly pluck protective magical artifacts out from his pouch and from his garments.

The senior Malfoy's voice cracked a little, with a bitter smile on his face. "Draco, Auror Moody already gave me the magical artifacts that I am allowed to use. You keep yours, and be safe yourself."

Draco's hand trembled, and his entire body tensed up.

From the hatred in the blond boy's eyes, Harry feared that Draco might be able to manage a killing curse toward Mad-Eye at this very moment. It was all good if your subordinates had some friendly rivalry, but mortal hatred was something Harry had to avoid. He needed to form a rescue plan, fast. "Ahh, Lord Malfoy, I think there is a highly useful charm that you may be able to learn now. With a few tricks, the Patronus charm can deliver messages and provide you with more protection."

The white-haired ex-Death Eater was unsure, "Lord Potter, I have tried after I know about Draco's, but -"

Harry eyed the old auror who was about to say something, and pleaded. "Privacy charms, please?"

Mad-Eye gave an angry grunt, and applied a number of privacy charms around Harry, Draco, Lucius and himself. As the outside became blurs, the old auror's magical eye was constantly on Lucius.

Then Harry spoke in Parseltongue. "There iss ssome trickss that Sseveruss can teach you, sso a killing cursse may not kill you insstantly. I am not ssure, I only tried it once."

Lucius looked at Harry in open shock. Slowly, he spoke with a frown, "that iss how… Oh. Ressurrection and killing cursse are opposite of each other? Sseveruss ssaid he ssacrificed ssome of hiss magic and life to bring me back, and he wanted me to live than to die…"

-Well, Lucius is smart, and his intuitions are good. He had thought that I was the Dark Lord after Hermione's trial, and in a sense, he was right.

"Auror Moody, would you free me for a while? I shall try as Lord Potter suggested." Lucius said, then turned to Harry and hissed. "No intention to hurt you or yourss, or to run away. Only tesst Patronuss charm."

Harry nodded to Mad-Eye. The old auror grudgingly removed some magical restrictions from Lucius, then aimed his wand at Lucius' chest, "should I trust your cunning, Malfoy?"

Lucius gave Mad-Eye a cold look, and accepted the snake-headed cane that Draco handed him. The ex-Death Eater took the stance, and twisted the wand precisely while looking at his son. "Expecto Patronum!"

A faint layer of bright silver smoke came out of the wand tip. Harry guessed that smoke might be able to hold-off dementors, but it was definitely not enough to block the killing curse.

Lucius looked at Harry, frowning. "Iss there ssomething that I have not guesssed out yet?"

Harry wasn't exactly sure how a Version 1.5 patronus worked, and as for more information…

Slytherin sneered, Lucius can't manage a truth patronus even if he is told the secrets, why are you hesitating whether to tell him the true secret?

Then Hufflepuff quietly suggested, although the true patronus may be hard for most people, but we should let Draco and Mad-Eye know the secrets of Severus' patronus. They are also in danger now, remember?

"Mr. Moody, is Professor Snape here yet? If so, could you let him in?" Harry asked.

A moment later, the unkempt ex-Potions master walked in with a strong smell of sewage, and his expensive robe - possibly given to him by Narcissa and Draco - was spotted with sludge and moss.

Before Severus and Mad-Eye could enter another round of stare contest, Harry quickly said, "Professor Snape, could you tell the secrets of your patronus to Draco, Lucius and Mr. Moody? My guesses are it can help to block the killing curse in case you absolutely can't dodge it. It may not stop the curse completely, but it may help to increase the chance of survival."

"What?" Both the normal eye and the magical eye of Alastor Moody became enlarged, then his face twisted. "Son, are you sure Snape should?"

Severus and Draco was quite shocked as well.

"I don't want any of you to encounter more danger than you absolutely have to." Harry said firmly, every part the Boy-Who-Lived that he was.

Severus slowly nodded, and said. "The emotion needed to fuel my patronus is not something traditional considered happy thoughts. I would imagine the grief and emotion of rejection as I heard the death of someone I cared, and I need to imagine how good it would be if the deceased could be alive. Some happy memories about that particular person would also help."

Draco, Lucius and Mad-Eye fell into silence for a while. Then Draco pulled out his old wand from his pouch, and took the stance. The blond boy looked at his revived father with tears glistening in his eyes, and shouted: "Expecto Patronum!"

A basketball-sized bright ball jumped out of Draco's wand tip.

Draco seemed to be surprised by his own patronus, then looked at his father, as if unsure of whether he should have done that.

Lucius smiled to his son with encouragement, proud and a hint of loss, "Draco, my son, you are truly an adult and a Lord Malfoy today." The blond man waved his snake-headed wand, and said, "Expecto Patronum."

A bright ball that was slightly smaller and fainter than Draco's exited the Malfoy family wand, and approached Draco's patronus. If light balls could hug, Harry would say that the two patronuses were hugging each other.

Lucius looked at the merging pure lights with some longing, as if hoping this moment could last forever, then asked, "Auror Moody, can we invite my wife Narcissa in for the ceremony?"

Mad-Eye ignored Lucius, deep in his own thoughts. Then the old auror snarled. "Damn it, too many have died! Expecto Patronum!"

A large aura of pure light left Moody's wand. For less than half a second, Harry thought he might have seen neck and shoulder, but the cloud consolidated into a large ball instead.

"I guess there is still some riddle that I need to solve." Mad-Eye twisted his wand back at Lucius.

"Believe me, you can't do it even if you have solved the riddle, so don't waste your time." Severus smirked. "And I gather neither you nor I has the need to kill dementors anyway, that is, of course, in case you can have the few reserved ones in check."

Mad-Eye gave Severus a suspicious look, grunted something, and started to wave his wand.

Harry looked at the smirking black-haired man in shock and admiration: Severus has solved the riddle?! He is surely sharper in magic than I thought. And a note to self: understanding the secrets of powerful magic, even the light ones, does not mean one can perform those, the same goes with Hermione's inability to cast the killing curse.

As Narcissa walked into the circle, the tall and slim witch held her wand tight, her eyes half on her husband and son, and half on Mad-Eye who was jabbing her with a number of charms and interesting looking magical devices. Narcissa was as elegantly dressed as her husband, but her blue eyes were blood-shot, puffy circles were visible through make-ups and beautification charms, and her cheeks were a bit shallower than Harry saw her last time.

After Mad-Eye reluctantly finished his checking, Narcissa smiled as if nothing bothersome had happened, and reached into her pouch. "Auror Moody, I was wholeheartedly delighted to hear that your colleagues have enjoyed my cookies, so I have prepared some more."

As the old auror's magical eye darted back and forth between the large luxuriously decorated box with snake ribbons and the innocent looking noblewoman, Harry could tell this was a deliberate move to create more work for the old auror who was constantly on guard.

Narcissa then turned to her husband who was smirking with proud and encouragement, "Lucius, my dear, I am so happy that you can be in Draco's ceremony today."

"Yes, my darling, our son is truly a grown man today." Lucius' smirk was replaced by a genuine smile as he pointed to the two hugging light balls, his head perceptibly higher, and spoke with a quiet pride, "and I am pleased that Draco has found broader light of life now."

Draco opened his mouth at this point, as if he wanted to say something to his father, but an assured smile from Lucius stopped him.

"That is -" Narcissa looked at the patronuses, a little unsure.

"Draco's patronus and mine; aren't they beautiful together?" Lucius reached out, and petted the brighter of the two hugging patronuses, while Draco blushed a little.

Mad-Eye's normal eye rolled, while his magical eye jumped all directions with some emphasis on the Malfoys as usual. "Be quick, you are wasting your own borrowed time!" He snarled.

Narcissa's eyes widened, then horrible apprehension began to appear on her face.

Lucius smiled to his wife, and then turned to Draco. The white-haired Malfoy patriarch put the snake-headed cane firmly into Draco's hand. His voice was smooth and unequivocal. "Draco Lucius Malfoy, my dear son, you are a true adult and a true Lord Malfoy today. "

Then Lucius took the three-snake ring handed to him by Narcissa, and put it on Draco's left middle finger. "Draco, bone of my bone and flesh of my flesh, may you have eternal health and happiness, may the world flourish because of you, and you will be the greatest Lord Malfoy that has yet lived."

As Lucius embraced Draco in his arms and kissed his forehead, Harry could tell that Draco was about to cry, but the new Lord Malfoy suppressed his emotions in front of Mad-Eye who was pointing his wand at them.

Then Narcissa also hugged Draco, and gave her blessings. "Draco, my son, fruit of my loins, may you have strength and wisdom, may you find love and marry a wonderful bride, and may you father many magical children."

Draco visibly blushed at his mother's blessings, and the fever became more heated when Narcissa kissed his forehead and cheeks.

Severus stepped in front of his new godson, and cleared his throat, some softness foreign to those black eyes took an effort to emerge. "Draco, my son in the eyes of the gods above and our ancestors in Atlantis, may you gain knowledge and powerful magic, -" the man stopped for a while, as if searching for words, "may you find true friendship." The black-haired man seemed to have fallen back to his comfort zone as he added his last sentence, "and I shall do my best to offer my protection and guidance."

When Severus wrapped his arms around his slender godson, the man was a bit stiff in his movements. Severus quickly brushed his lips on Draco's forehead, then patted Draco's shoulder.

"Alright, Lucius Malfoy, it's time for you to do your job now." Mad-Eye's words won him stares from Severus and the Malfoys.

"Emm, there's one more thing," Harry interjected, "I need to go and properly threaten the dementors the aurors brought here, so that they can respond to Lucius' mental calling if he encounters You-Know-Who."

Lucius raised one eyebrow, then nodded politely to Harry. "No words can describe my gratitude, Lord Potter."

Slytherin quietly said, well, Lucius knows dementors work by expectations anyway. And should we give us plus one point in manipulation for letting Mad-Eye be the bad guy and appearing benign ourselves?

Shut up.

Note:

In canon, Book 2, the young Tom Riddle had said in Parseltongue "Speak to me, Slytherin, the greatest of Hogwarts Four" to open the gate for Salazar's monster. Therefore, in canon, Parseltongue did contain names.

If we assume Salazar built Parseltongue based on his own knowledge, why would such a proud man who called himself "the greatest of Hogwarts Four" not include his own name in the language?

Moreover, making up translations of people's names can't be too different from making up nouns that describes magical items, such as horcrux. In the process of conjuring hundreds and thousands of nouns describing spells, rituals, and lore into Parseltongue, it was quite reasonable to include people's names, especially in the lore part.

Third, a lot of names in Harry Potter did exist in Salazar's time, and it is reasonable to believe he knew them. Lucius, Severus and Draco are relatively common names in ancient Rome; Hermione, Minerva are names of goddesses in Greek/Roman mythology; Harry/Henry/Harrold is a common English name since the Middle Ages. I assume Salazar should know these names from his Latin learning or pursuit of Greek/Roman lore or just by teaching in Hogwarts, though I admit Salazar might not know the names such as Xiaoguang Li or Padma Patil.

I am sorry that I need to postpone the next update, because I am waiting for my betas to give me feedback on my next chapter.

Chapter 27: The Search, Pt IV, Sacrifices

All my thanks to Jared, Joe, and Kuilin, who beta-ed this chapter.

10:44 am, June 28th, 1993

In a small circle of privacy in the headquarter office, Harry, Hermione, Draco and Madam Bones were all focusing their attention at a newly installed large two-way screen.

The screen showed the hastily-emptied transfiguration research room, where only the stone platform to perform experiments on was left. Lucius stood on the platform, pondering something with a temporary wand in his hands. Mad-Eye Moody stood on the side of the platform, quite ready to throw a number of interesting hexes on the ex-Lord Malfoy if the blond man dared to do anything extra. In the meantime, Severus was looking back and forth between the rat in the cage besides Lucius and the blond man with unreadable eyes.

Harry also took a great interest in Lucius' demonstration on two different levels: Can Lucius' great invention actually work? If so, what does this mean for the current war?

Lucius took the Patronus stance, and twisted his temporary wand in two circles and one slash in the middle. As if putting his life and magic into the wand, Lucius shouted, "Protego Vitamaxima!"

A bright white-blue shield sprang out from Lucius' wand's tip. The shield was brighter and more solid than any shield that Harry had ever seen, which should be impossible considering Lucius' impaired magical level.

Then Severus pointed his wand at Lucius' shield, but away from Lucius' person. "Reducto!"

The blasting hex rebounded off the powerful shield as expected.

Severus went one step up with the curses. "Sectumsempra!"

The powerful cutting hex invented by Severus himself was blocked by the shield as well.

"Crucio!" Severus shouted.

This time Lucius' shield cracked a little, and the blond man became a little whiter, but the curse was still blocked.

"I think it would be best if we put it to the ultimate test soon, for my magic may not last long." Sweat began to show on Lucius' forehead.

Mad-Eye sneered, stunned the rat, transfigured its face into something resembling Voldemort's snake-like face, and put it on top of the cage.

Lucius then tilted his shield to be more on the rat than himself, and nodded to Severus nervously.

The dark-haired man slightly closed his eyes, then focused on the face of the rat.

Harry knew that it was difficult for anyone with level-one knowledge of the killing curse to hate a rat enough to cast it, which was why Mad-Eye had transfigured the rat's face, helping Severus trick his mind.

The ex-spy cast. "Avada Kedavra!"

A bolt of green light exited Severus' black wand, hitting the bright-blue shield. Some green light was shattered while the shield cracked, dimmed, and winked out. At the same time, both Lucius and Severus began to scream upon the contact of their magic, both instinctively dodging to avoid the scattering green light. Then, both ex-Death Eaters threw away their wands as previously instructed by Harry.

The scream and twitching of the two ex-Death Eaters became subdued after their wands were out of their hands, while the high-pitched desperate shriek of another animal became quite obvious.

The rat on top of the cage was clearly tortured, but it was still alive.

Everyone looked at the tortured rat with amazed eyes. Severus groaned, "The pain I endured was just a bit worse than Crucio, but the residual magic that passed through the shield was not even enough to kill a rat."

At any other time, Harry would be absolutely delighted by Lucius' great insight that could block the killing curse, which was a great step in the mission of conquering death. Harry might want the Wizengamot to give Lucius an Order of Merlin for it, and might even argue for a one-hundred-year reduction in prison time for Lucius. However, at this moment, Harry could only ask one question: is Lucius really the inventor of this spell? If not, in the name of Merlin, what happened?

About twenty minutes ago, when Severus heard Lucius talking about the stance, gesture, and incantation of the proposed spell, he sneered: "Lucius, you do not become a charms master on par with Albus Dumbledore or the Dark Lord the moment you feel the need for a new orientation in life, even if your life depends on it. Guessing the secret behind a powerful spell or ritual, maybe. However, working out the stance, gesture, and incantation within the time interval of searching one pipeline? It is simply impossible, even for the likes of Dumbledore! Or are you claiming yourself to be -"

Severus stopped in mid-sentence, and instead asked Lucius to perform the spell. The moment the dark-haired man saw a seemingly solid white-blue shield, he called for help from Alastor Moody. When Mad-Eye answered that he couldn't turn back in time, Severus apologized, threw all the binding spells he could on Lucius, before dragging the white-haired man to the transfiguration research room.

After Mad-Eye rushed to the room, he frisked Lucius with all the diagnostic spells and trinkets he could think of, finding nothing abnormal. Then he proposed a final test result that could only show up once during Lucius' current life span, anytime between 12:45 am and 6:45 am this June 30th.

"If there is no Time-Turner involved, the ex-Lord Malfoy would be completely fine until about 6 am, June 30th. If any symptoms show up before that, well, I guess we know the result. So, Lucius, you'd better tell us all the truth," Mad-Eye snarled viciously.

Lucius was properly panicked by the test that Mad-Eye proposed, and protested loudly, "You have promised to use the Stone on me after twenty-four hours, not forty-eight! Am I supposed to believe that this is not a scheme of yours to simply kill me? I know you want to. How am I to know if your transfiguration is timed well enough?"

Harry knew the test Mad-Eye proposed was a good one to know whether a Time-Turner was involved in Lucius' case. However, there were multiple questions involved: first, Mad-Eye is a perfect occlumens who can't speak Parseltongue, so there is no convenient way to know whether Mad-Eye is telling what is perceived by himself to be the truth, such as how many hours the transfiguration was supposed to last; second, even if Mad-Eye is telling the truth, the Confundus Charm and memory charms, along with a number of other things, are still a danger; third, nobody has tested Mad-Eye's transfiguration precision besides himself, and it is known that people tend to exaggerate their own abilities in their own minds; fourth and most importantly, the test subject, one Lucius Malfoy, is in lethal danger, and he objects the test with good grounds.

Therefore, Harry proposed another test: just let Lucius cast the spell he thought might block the killing curse along with other hexes. If the shield failed, it could be a highly-unwise whim of Lucius, but if it was successful like now…

Harry had no choice but to consider some sinister explanations.

Lucius had claimed in Parseltongue that he didn't know that anything abnormal had happened - there just might have been a slight disorientation, but that could have been caused by the fact that he hadn't had any breakfast that morning, and then he had crawled in pipelines for three hours with an empty stomach.

To Harry, the slight disorientation strongly suggested a Time-Turner and memory charms, though Lucius himself might prefer the other explanation. The blond man argued that since the remembrall handed to him hadn't glowed, and he had invented a hair-smoothing spell when he was fifteen, and a robe-shaping charm when he was sixteen, therefore this new spell must be his own invention.

-Because everyone would like to believe themselves to be a genius. Acquiring the ability to figure out details of a powerful spell takes years of hard learning. Even after that, it would take much longer than a few hours for most wizards who are as brilliant as Dumbledore to do it.

Harry didn't need to say this part, because Mad-Eye said it for him. "A remembrall is such a weak magical item. I have a dozen ways to fool it, I'm sure Voldie has at least that. I wouldn't be surprised if you formulated a conspiracy to overthrow the Wizengamot in half an hour, but crafting a spell? Pfft. Are you suggesting that you are as smart as your previous master? If so, why don't you go and hunt down the bastard, and give us his head in exchange for the use of the Stone?"

"How could the Dark Lord possibly conjure up some spell involving the Patronus charm?" Lucius argued reasonably. "Moreover, why am I alive? Why are you alive? Why is Draco unscathed?"

Mad-Eye snarled, "Perhaps you defected back to the Dark Lord, and told him everything about the Patronus charm."

"And you think that he would let me go just because I told him the secret behind a spell that he couldn't cast?" Lucius rebutted sarcastically. "Not even Dumbledore would let me go unscathed. I wonder how you became delusional enough to believe the Dark Lord suddenly became a saint."

"Maybe he plotted to get to Harry through you, and this great spell was only imprinted to your memory because he wanted Harry Potter to observe the effect himself. Probably there is some trigger that would only be activated by the presence of Harry, or Hermione, or something on their body, etc. Good thing that Severus directly dragged you here. You can claim your innocence all you want in Parseltongue now, but when the time comes, you will bring disaster the moment something is triggered, you vile snake!" Mad-Eye stopped, and his lips twitched. "Maybe he would want you not only to bring him Harry Potter, but also the new Lord Malfoy. Then, he will let you torture your own precious son to death yourself, or let you torture each other to death."

Lucius' face turned a shade whiter when he heard Mad-Eye's proposed scenarios.

Harry knew what Mad-Eye proposed was entirely possible for the Voldemort the old Auror knew, but now Harry had another explanation: Voldemort is practicing being nice.

-A Version 1.0 Patronus is impossible for Voldemort, because that psychopath probably can never be happy enough to cast the Patronus charm; the true Patronus is impossible for him as well, for he doesn't value the lives of others. However, a Version 1.5 Patronus may actually work for him, because Voldemort may be able to think how great it is for himself to live while rejecting his own death.

Harry cursed himself again for being too slow for the uptake, being too loose on important secrets, and -

-Hermione didn't stop me, because she wanted everyone to have the maximum probability of survival as I do; Draco might have seen the danger, but he didn't stop me, because he wanted to increase his father's chances to live.

Oh, are you trying to blame your friends for your mistakes? What kind of hero are you? Hufflepuff chided Harry. I thought we had all agreed on the heroic responsibility thing. And it is neither Hermione nor Draco's responsibility to prevent world destruction, but we dragged them into it.

-I am just stating the facts, not blaming them.

That rebuttal won Harry a sour face from Hufflepuff and a sneer from his internal-consistency checker.

Somewhere in the back of Harry's mind, he could imagine Professor Quirrell's cold sardonic laughs: when the Dark Lord does something nice, the "good" people just quarrel amongst themselves more!

"I can see why." Madam Bones spoke gravely. "The Dark Lord is using a good person or multiple good persons as pawns. In the Azkaban breakout, I thought he had told some extensive lies to a good, clever, and powerful person to deceive him or her into rescuing Bellatrix Black, because that person subdued Bahry without killing him, and that person used transfigured water as rocker fuel so that the Aurors wouldn't be badly hurt when the transfiguration wore out."

-Although we know what really happened in Azkaban, Madam Bones' idea is another possibility. Voldemort might have used some good and powerful wizards as pawns. For example, Voldemort took on the identity of Alexander Chernyshov. It is reasonable to believe that some of his followers back then were genuinely good people, and they were absolutely loyal to him. He might even have taught some supporters some powerful magic to keep up appearances. Voldemort could have easily gone to supporters like that. He could tell them the sole reason he had disappeared for so long, was that he was killed and remained as only an incorporeal ghost, sustained by a horcrux he made when he slayed an evil enemy. He might have told his supporters that Lucius was his enemy for some made-up reason - Lucius wasn't a good person anyway - and told his supporters to get Lucius' blood. Or, he might have told his supporters that he needed Lucius' blood for some good reason, so his supporters would do it more willingly.

-And one of Voldemort's powerful supporters might have felt sorry for taking Lucius' blood and mind-charming him, so he or she left a cue of a recently invented powerful protection spell to Lucius. And he or she might think letting giant spiders kill each other was a good thing to do as well. Or the last part was Professor Quirrell's act.

-As for flesh from a servant, that's no problem for Voldemort at all.

-Father's bone, hmm, maybe Voldemort had cut his father's body into pieces, and buried the pieces over a wide region near Earth's surface.

-At any rate, dementors are probably no longer a powerful weapon against Voldemort. Or, is that another bluff on Voldemort's part, like the time that he tricked us to doubt the Hogwarts wards?

As Harry began to think about the Hogwarts wards, he started to miss the Map that could show everyone's name within Hogwarts. When the Aurors burned everything besides Professor Quirrell's body, the Map was burned as well. At the time, Harry had considered it rather convenient, fearing someone else might find out that the Hogwarts wards considered him to be Tom Riddle.

Therefore, when Mad-Eye included the true-name system of the Hogwarts wards into the protection on the Room of Requirement, Harry made no suggestion as to try to make another Map to cover the entire range of Hogwarts, but rather he made a mental note to himself not to go anywhere near the Room of Requirement.

-Now, if we had the Map…

No, Harry needed to stop blaming himself, because that could wait. He needed to think of something useful.

-If I were Voldemort, what would I do?

Harry started to model Voldemort in his mind.

-Blood purity is nonsense, since I, a half-blood, am the most powerful wizard in the world, so I wouldn't need Lucius' blood for its purity. Lucius is not a powerful wizard, therefore his blood is inferior. I would definitely need something better.

-For example, I would need Hermione Granger's blood, since she is quite powerful on her own accord, and her blood contains the power of a unicorn and a troll.

-On the other hand, I may also have some powerful enemies in some other parts of the world. Their blood may also suffice.

-I would still want the Stone. Hmm, the nice version of wanting the Stone would be to use a false identity, fake some dangerous condition, and let the healers send me to the Hospital. I have ample time to do that before Bellatrix's body decays, or even after her body decays, because I have other loyal servants who would die for me without any questions being asked.

-Plus, confusing my enemies, showing my omnipotence, and being nice in the meantime are rather fun.

"I think this is a backup plan for the Dark Lord," Harry said grimly. "He wouldn't be satisfied by anything less than Hermione's blood."

Harry could see that Lucius wanted to sneer but quickly caught himself, and Hermione gasped slightly before her hand covered her mouth.

"I think Voldie would prefer yours, but the Girl-Who-Revived's might barely do," Mad-Eye pondered.

-No, there is the magical resonance thing, so he wouldn't use my blood for his revival. Plus, he wouldn't risk himself with me again, not until he got all his power back.

Harry didn't say it, because other dark wizards might have wanted his blood for some unrelated evil ritual, and continued to model Voldemort.

-What would I do after I obtained a lesser enemy's blood, and had everything I need for a lesser revival ritual?

-I might obtain more blood from lesser enemies. I have quite a bunch of them all over the world. And I would need a plot to get the best blood I can, of course.

-Moreover, the Stone. I would need to obtain the Stone. And I would need to kill the younger Tom Riddle.

-Or better. If I threatened the younger Tom Riddle with world destruction and promised not to destroy the world myself, my younger self might steal the Stone for me and kill himself. Yeah, the world would be safer with the younger Tom Riddle dead, and I would be doing a nice thing. However, the boy might pull a trick on me again, so this would be just another backup plan.

-The world might be boring without my younger self, so I may throw him into the Mirror and save him for my later entertainment.

-Oh, the Mirror!

Harry had a grim smile on his young face. He now knew what he should do. All the time, he always knew what he should do, he just avoided thinking of it because it was just too painful.

-I can invoke the ritual that Dumbledore used, which he left some instructions for in the secret room in the Headmaster's office. I can lock myself and all other Tom Riddles in Time. With some maneuver, I may even be able to get Dumbledore out in the process.

-I should give this thing a countdown clock as a dead-man's switch, where I need to periodically send a signal to reset the countdown within a certain period of time, or otherwise the Mirror will lock all Tom Riddles in Time. No, it should be a combination of positive triggers and negative triggers.

-Since dementors work on expectations, incorporating them in the ritual as remote controls would be a good idea. And since Voldemort only guessed how dementors worked after he killed MacNair, the current Horcrux Voldemort probably doesn't know.

-To be safe, I need to figure out multiple ways to trigger this ritual. A brainstorm with Mad-Eye, Severus, Hermione, and Draco may produce some.

-The disappearance of one good person together with potentially many other evil ones, and a much safer world. Just what a hero in a story should do.

-As for my other projects such as conquering death, Hermione and Draco might be able to do that. And after Hermione has lead sapient beings to conquer far-away galaxies or other universes, she might release all Tom Riddles from the Mirror, save me, and blast the ancient Earth plus the Pioneer plaques - no, the Milky Way Galaxy for safety precautions.

-That's definitely a working plan, which actually fits the Prophecies indicated by Dumbledore and Voldemort.

With a scarily bright smile on his face, the Boy-Who-Lived happily said, "Madam Bones, Mr. Moody, Professor Snape, Draco, and Hermione, I have something to talk about with each of you in private, and maybe some of you in groups."

8:14 pm, July 2nd, 1993 (local time)

A balding brown-haired white man in wizarding robes floated invisibly in the middle of the air, looking downward with cold and calculating eyes.

Beneath him, hundreds of Muggles in festive clothes were densely packed on a river boat decorated with a 20-foot tall pagoda, cheering happily, and thousands more were cheering for them on the river banks, for this was a well-attended local holiday on this heavily populated island.

The man drew out a brand-new black wand, and made a slight gesture.

A holiday firework shooting out from the river bank made a small departure from its original path, and took its aim at the holiday boat. Some people on the boat saw the stray firework that was shooting toward them, and tried to move away, while other people who couldn't see the rocket were pushed to the other side of the boat. The shift of the center of weight of the boat, with the help of some timely wind on the top of the pagoda, tilted the barge. As some cracking noises from the boat were heard, the mass on the boat became panicked.

With a wave of his hand, a large piece of parchment and a quill invisible to the crowd below appeared in front of the man in the middle of the air. As Muggles fell into the river like cherries falling into a washing pan, the calls from Muggles took a sudden turn from happiness to panic, the man occasionally twitched his wand and murmured something low in an ancient language.

As men, women, and children who were good swimmers their whole lives found themselves unable to keep themselves afloat in the warm July water, the quill in the middle of the air would note down something on the parchment.

The balding man frowned: hmm, drowning doesn't work so well. Do I have to build a gas chamber myself?

When a hint of blackness began to form over the river where hundreds of people were drowning, the brown-haired wizard instantly gathered his quill and parchment, and apparated away.

-It seems that the formation of dementors are another concern of this method, but this surely proves that massive deaths of Muggles do have some magical effect. Did Grindelwald use some method to prevent dementors from forming, or did he use some method to channel the magic elsewhere, or did he use someone with a Patronus to help him? Hmm.

Chapter 28: Memory Charms

All my thanks to Jared, Joe, and Kuilin, who beta-ed this chapter.

11:57 pm, July 2nd, 1993

Accompanied by an Auror trio, Severus walked slowly through the stone hallways of Hogwarts, slightly dazed. He and Mad-Eye had escorted Harry back to his bed chamber in Ravenclaw, where an Auror trio would guard the Boy-Who-Lived for the night, and Mad-Eye had just departed through the Floo in Minerva's office.

Usually, Severus would prefer a solitary walk in an almost-empty Hogwarts at night. However, the current security protocol required that nobody should ever pass through the corridors alone. What was worse, to the dismay of both Severus and the current Auror trio, Severus and Auror Bahry had to share what used to be Severus' temporary living room, while the place Severus had called his bedroom for a few days was shared by Auror McJorgenson and Trainee Auror Tonks.

Any other time, Severus would hate this rather inconsiderate arrangement; but he knew his current daze, caused by multiple advanced memory charms, might impair his ability to defend himself for a short while - so he tolerated the presence of the Auror trio for now.

-Well, my patience will run out when the women begin their long showers, while Bahry and I have to wait for our turns. Merlin knows why women can take showers together, while Bahry and I would rather hex each other than do the same. Perhaps that's because Tonks and McJorgenson like each other, while Bahry and I despise each other.

Severus gave an inward sigh and dearly hoped this safety protocol would end soon.

-To be honest, who are we kidding? The glasses we are wearing at all times may prevent immediate death by basilisk attacks, but the Dark Lord can probably kill all of us without any magic. Even I can think of Muggle explosives. The Dark Lord can surely think of something better.

-And the Boy-Who-Lived's plot, whatever it is, will it work?

Severus frowned slightly, wondering what the things that he didn't remember now were. He remembered that Harry Potter had called him into the Headmistress' Office four days ago after Hermione, Draco, and Mad-Eye each had their own talks with the Boy-Who-Lived. Potter had asked Severus whether he would participate in something and then be memory-charmed about it,only recalling part of it after certain events occurred. Severus had surely agreed.

-The Girl-Who-Revived seemed a bit sad after her talk with Potter, so whatever the plot is, it must require some sacrifices on our side. Would that boy be stupid enough to really act Dumbledore-ish, and sacrifice himself? That's surely a possibility.

Severus felt a familiar wave of sadness and nausea.

-If only we can somehow preserve the boy's head when he sacrifices himself, maybe I can revive him.

-Otherwise, I can only hope one of three things turn out our way. First, Potter is creative enough that he will think of something powerful enough to defeat the Dark Lord again using the lessons that Mad-Eye and I are about to teach him. Second, my future attempt to corrupt magical officials of the former Soviet states may result in some interesting discoveries, and the boy may get something more from those. Third, as Lucius has offered, he may be able to weasel out some secrets from Grindelwald after he is sentenced.

-Grindelwald had been literally invincible before his Muggle allies failed - or at least that was what Albus claimed, though I never asked Albus the question in Parseltongue - so there must be something there. Nazis had notorious concentration camps that killed Muggles in very meticulous manners: could that be the secret? If so, can we use the natural deaths of Muggles to boost Potter's magic for a while? Tens of thousands Muggles die from natural causes every day anyway.

The ex-Death Eater continued his thought that would definitely be condemned by the "good" people of magical Britain as he entered his temporary residence. When the women went to the bathroom, Bahry and Severus stared at each other, before they each went into their own beds with curtains drawn.

Severus reached into his pouch, drawing out his dark-blue suitcase containing most of his books, and descended into his suitcase-study.

Severus' plan for tonight had been learning Russian in preparation for his future trip to whichever former Soviet states had enough secrets and plenty of corruptible magical officials, but his heart wasn't exactly in Russian now. For some reason Severus had a feeling that if he were to learn ancient runes or Egyptian hieroglyphs tonight, he might gain more.

-Is this related to what I did for the past three days? Is it possible that the Boy-Who-Lived knew something from his Line of Merlin Unbroken heritage, and asked Mad-Eye and me to perform the magic for him? The knowledge might not be Interdicted, but ancient and powerful for sure. Or, the boy had guessed the secret of some Interdicted magic, and just needed us to fill in the details.

Severus sat down by his solid wooden desk, adjusted the light in the study, and summoned the Advanced Magical Hieroglyphs that he had duplicated from Hogwarts library, and the Ancient Egyptian Hieroglyphs that he had duplicated from the British library.

Severus sighed inwardly for the wizarding kind: even in the language that is considered magical, the Muggles know more these days. Should I feel lucky the wizards hired by the goblins to work in the pyramids don't study Muggle Egyptology? There might still be something left for me to discover there.

-Maybe after we get rid of the Dark Lord once and for all, I can explore Latin America, Egypt, Iraq, Iran, India, China, and Japan as I originally planned. Actually, I should travel to Iraq and Iran first, before the Muggles start another war in the region and destroy everything.

Severus looked longingly at his large collection of mostly-untouched language and history books that he duplicated with the help of several memory charmed and bribed Muggle librarians in the British Library. He knew all his planning would only be dreaming if the Boy-Who-Lived's plan didn't work out.

After Severus had flipped through quite some pages in his third read-through of Ancient Egyptian Hieroglyphs, Auror Bahry yelled something outside the suitcase, and Severus ignored him.

-Let him take the bath first. The hieroglyphs are really beginning to make sense to me now.

However, by this time, Severus started to feel some emptiness in his stomach. Severus murmured, "Tempus."

"12:42 am, July 3rd, 1993" showed up in the air.

Severus then drew out his mechanical pocket watch from his pouch, and it showed 6:42 am.

-I must have somehow turned my Time-Turner six times in the past twenty-four hours, for some purpose that I don't remember. And as a matter of fact, when did I have my last meal?

Severus shook his head, trying to get the light fog of tiredness and the after-effect of memory charms away, and summoned a frozen burger from his pouch. While heating the burger, Severus absent-mindedly noted that the memory charms he or someone else had used on him must be quite strong, since he was still feeling the after-effect.

-However, there is something not quite right. What is it?

Severus opened his pouch and dug into it, hoping he had left himself a note or some other form of communication.

Chapter 31: Descendants Pt III, Lucius Malfoy

All my thanks to Jared, Joe, and Kuilin, who beta-ed this chapter.

10:14 am, June 28th, 1993

From the sparse Parseltongue dialogue and whatever Salazar could guess from conversations in vernacular, he had gathered that Lucius was now held as a political prisoner, while little Draco was serving as a lieutenant for the young Tom Riddle. Salazar could guess why this was the case: Tom Riddle wants to separate little Draco from his father, so he can better manipulate little Draco. Moreover, he can use Lucius to threaten Draco, or use Draco to manipulate Lucius. That's why Draco goes into the Forbidden Forest to face cannibalistic giant spiders, and why Lucius is searching in pipelines for the unknown threat, aka, me. This young Tom Riddle also controls Severus with some leverage I haven't figured out yet.

The games that the younger Tom Riddle were playing contained some basic manipulation techniques that Salazar had used, but when it came to some descendant Salazar disliked manipulating some descendants who had entertained Salazar, it was a different matter.

Therefore, Salazar needed to evaluate the worthiness of Lucius and Severus the Stutterer, to see if he needed to plot something to free these boys from Tom Riddles.

The result of the evaluation was quite unexpected.

Directing Lucius into an empty classroom temporarily hidden from anyone else's eyes was quite amusing. Salazar shifted the sewer that Lucius was in toward the empty classroom, and called through the pipelines: "Greetingss, desscendant of Angitia and Draco, I mean you no harm."

The mirror spell Salazar put in the sewer told him that the poor blue snake with black stripes completely froze, and the entire body turned a shade whiter. Obviously, Lucius assumed that Salazar was the older Tom Riddle whom he was looking for.

-Oh, wait. Hoodwinked by Tom Riddles as Lucius is, mentally calling for dementors is indeed a cunning idea, at least, a good idea against the "evil" older Tom Riddle.

Salazar accessed Hogwarts wards, partially activated the ban on dementors installed after Lord Foul's attempt to use them in his attack, and called again, "Come forward, Luciuss. Those dirty creaturess are banned from entering, but a clever thought if ussed elssewhere."

The blue snake began to crawl reluctantly toward the only exit, while Salazar pondered how he should test Lucius' worthiness. He knew Lucius was weak in magic, but that could be a result of the Unbreakable Vow they had talked about. As for resourcefulness, Lucius definitely possessed some basic cunning, so he needed to use some advanced techniques to probe for higher level intelligence.

Just before entering the empty classroom, the blue snake animagus suddenly rushed and leapt toward the exit, twisting into human form the moment he entered the empty classroom, while a number of defensive magical items were triggered at the same time.

With a wave of wand, all the magical trinkets winked out, and the temporary wand in the starting gesture of a stunning hex also flew out from Lucius' hand. Salazar waved his wand again, the blond man was fully binded, including his opening mouth and twitching fingers that were undoubtedly trying to activate something.

Salazar showed himself in front of Lucius, and appraised the man with long white mane. He found more traces of his grandson-in-law in this grown man's features, for the first Draco was just a few years younger than this Lucius when Salazar left. The garments on the white-faced Lucius looked no less expensive than little Draco, his nails and hair were well-cared for, which meant Lucius was doing relatively alright as a prisoner, another proof of his cunning. The blue-grey eyes behind the glasses were appraising Salazar as well, which meant he hadn't given up while facing a much stronger unknown wizard.

"Do not confusse me with any lessser wizardss, Luciuss." Salazar said matter-of-factly. "I am the Greatesst of Hogwartss Four, and the King of Sserpent. I am Ssalazar Sslytherin."

Lucius' eyes widened as expected, and from a quickly suppressed sign of suspicion, he didn't fully believe Salazar just because Salazar stated his identity in Parseltongue.

-Of course, I wouldn't believe others just because they said something in Parseltongue, because people can be memory charmed to believe that they are someone else. However, Lucius needs to train his face better, or is he playing at a level higher?

"Before I let you sspeak, no, I do not dessire to be involved in the current war fought by my desscendantss." Salazar would rather prefer that his descendants were at peace with each other, but he didn't say that he wouldn't get involved in the war, did he?

Then Salazar threw Lucius a question that the blond man clearly didn't expect. "How large iss the world?"

Although Salazar was most interested in how to get to the Stone, he was indeed quite interested in the question he asked. Nagini had mentioned that quite some Interdicted spells Tom Riddle learnt were from an island nation "where the ssun rissess", which was further away than India or China. The furthest point Salazar had traveled was Isfahan in Persia, and he was quite interested in what existed in the world unknown to him, especially, Atlantis.

With another wave of wand, Lucius was able to speak. The blond man answered, "Earth iss ball-sshaped, around eight-thoussand miless in diameter. There iss the New Continent, wesst of Atlantic Ocean -"

-Later wizards found Atlantis?

Salazar had to suppress himself from calling out.

"Many wizardss thought it wass Atlantiss when firsst found, but it wass not the casse. " Lucius continued his answer, "The ssame happened when another continent ssoutheasst of Assia, in the ssouthern hemissphere, wass found. Not Atlantiss. Many new isslandss were found, no Atlantiss."

Salazar was quite disappointed that Atlantis was not found. However, the way Lucius worded his answer did create some dramatic effects in Salazar's heart, if not on his face. This meant Lucius was trying to gain some upper-hand while providing new information, which was both annoying and somewhat to Salazar's taste.

"Powerful magic in other partss of the world wass found, though." Lucius continued. "I heard ssome wizardss in China reach magical agreements with powerful magical animalss, such ass ssnakess, foxess, and weasselss, and ssome really powerful magical animalss can adopt human formss."

-Hmm, it seems my basilisk idea is not that unique. By the way, are those "powerful magical animals" really animals, or are they powerful wizards with long-lived animagus forms? I have speculated the reason I am still relatively agile at this age, while many powerful wizards are no longer light-footed at around one hundred and forty, is my animagus form, which is a long-lived basilisk. Well, if I choose to spend most of my time as a basilisk, can I live a thousand years?

-By the way, Lucius can see where my question actually directs to. Good.

"And in -" Lucius paused, as if searching for words.

"You can usse Latin." Salazar realized that Parseltongue probably didn't contain the names of new found places.

"Can I draw a world map firsst?" Lucius grasped the chance, and asked. "Sso I can exxplain better."

-Cunning. Unfortunately for Lucius, I might have seen something from Giuliani's memory, but that small thing surely looked strange from his memory.

Salazar reached into Giuliani's pouch, and mentally called for the neatly binded small book he saw from the dark wizard's memory. What flew into his hand was a book only the size of the hand of an adult, and the parchment of the book was better polished than the finest lamb parchment that Salazar had ever seen. Salazar flipped a few pages of that book, and saw some meticulously drew graphs, and one of the graphs reminded Salazar of the shape of the Mediterranean Sea, so it must be a collection of maps. The scripts in the book were written in something resembling Latin, and the letters were definitely not written by hand, for there were no dents beneath the ink.

-There are so many things that I don't know.

Then Salazar started to project the graphs in the small book onto the blackboard in the classroom, and asked Lucius to explain.

As it turned out, the very first picture of the book was a world map. It took Salazar some time to understand the current cartography, and then Salazar was quite amazed by the vastness of the world.

Unlike most ignorant wizards in his time, Salazar knew for sure that the earth was a very large ball, and the sun was orbiting the earth. Actually, a wizard just needed to apparate eastward or westward to realize that the sun rose at different times at different locations; and one just needed to apparate northward or southward to observe the different angles of the sun at noon time. Moreover, Rowena had done some complex calculations, and proved that both Venus and Mars orbited around the sun, and the sun and the moon orbited around the earth. Unfortunately, something quite earthly took away the life of the first astronomy teacher in Hogwarts before she could delineate how Jupiter traveled.

Now, it seemed that later wizards had explored the Earth extensively, and Salazar, who had considered himself widely-traveled, had only been to a small fraction of the world. There were China and India where Salazar knew of but had never traveled to, the rest of Africa to the south of the great desert, the islands named "Japan" where Tom Riddle learnt a lot of his powerful magic, and the huge new continents named "America" and "Australia".

-I have definitely made the right decision as to lock myself into the Mirror. I have so many new goals now.

-Moreover, judging by how much the current wizards had improved the invention by Merlin's great-great granddaughter, could the current wizards have conquered the strong winds at great heights, and flown to the moon, the sun, and some stars? I would like to try.

"How about the sstarss?" Salazar asked.

Lucius became somewhat uneasy upon this question, and took in a deep breath before he answered, "Muggless ssay there are one hundred thoussand million sstarss in our galaxxy, and thoussandss and millionss of galaxiess. Light needs to travel sseveral minutess to the ssun, and sseveral yearss to the nearesst starss."

-Wait, Muggles? What do they have to do with the ancient and noble arts of astronomy?

"Why did you quote Muggless' wordss about sstarss?" Salazar hissed. He began to doubt Lucius' loyalty to the wizarding kind.

"It iss posssible that Muggless know more about the sstarss and can predict fate of the sstarss better nowadayss." Lucius' face was as white as chalk as he answered, "And according to a paper I jusst read yessterday, in - " Lucius changed into vernacular, said "American Mage", then changed back to Parseltongue, "The Muggless have ssomething called -", vernacular again, "nuclear weapon".

Lucius' lips twitched slightly before he spoke the last part, as if he was sure he would be killed the next second. "It iss ssaid to have something to do with why the ssun and sstarss sshine. The way it workss ressembless ritualss, as it sacrificess masss and leadss to huge explossion that destroyss citiess insstantly."

Salazar wasn't a good tempered man, but he had never killed any messenger who brought him bad news. Moreover, the bad news spoken in Parseltongue was simply too astonishing to Salazar.

Godric had been the holder of Line of Merlin Unbroken, therefore he had known a lot of Merlin's secrets. Soon after Hogwarts was built, Godric had gathered Salazar, Rowena, and Helga, and solemnly told them that there was a great danger that he only had some vague ideas of, and the other three needed to know of this danger for the preservation of all wizarding kind. It was a ritual that sacrificed mass, or "atomon", as defined by some ancient wizard in Greece. The ritual was only mentioned in some scratched notes by Merlin, and Merlin had to throw away his time and magic to build the Most Ancient Hall, so that the wizarding kind to have a chance to survive in case such ritual was ever invoked. Therefore, in case such unspeakable ritual was ever used against Hogwarts, they were not to resist, but to try to bring as many students as possible to the Most Ancient Hall.

-It can't possibly be the one that I am thinking of. But huge explosion that destroys cities, that does sound like what Godric warned us of.

"How doess it compared to Greek Fire?" Salazar asked about the most powerful weapon that Muggles of his days could use - made by wizards, of course, and it was beyond Salazar's understanding as why wizards in Constantinople made them usable by Muggles.

Lucius seemed to need a second to remember what "Greek Fire" was, and answered. "Much more powerful than Greek Fire. It iss reported that one mass-sacrificial weapon killed more than one hundred thousand Muggless about fifty yearss ago, and after two ssuch weaponss were ussed, a Muggle nation of seventy million people ssurrendered."

A Muggle nation of seventy million people - that, that was almost beyond Salazar's imagination.

-Was it somewhere around the total population of Roman Empire at the peak of its height? But if weapons that could invoke the ritual Godric warned us about were used, the only sensible action for a nation was to surrender.

Salazar briefly imagined the surrender of Roman Empire at the height of its glory, and he had to admit it to himself that although he had laughed at the pathetic Muggle rulers of the barbaric England, ruling a Muggle nation such as Roman Empire was pretty attractive. Actually, Salazar knew that several emperors of the Roman Empires were rumored to be wizards before the Roman Empire chose the wizard-persecuting Christianity as its official religion.

-However, if the power to let such a great nation surrender was controlled by some Muggle nation, the logical question is…

"Iss the Muggle world ruled by one nation now?" Salazar suppressed his true question, which was - "Are we sslavess of Muggless?"

To Salazar's relief and confusion, Lucius was quickly answered, "No, there are more than one hundred Muggle countriess in the world, and about half a dozen Muggle countriess used to have the weapon." Then the blond man added, "However, one of the weapon-wielding countriess collapssed two yearss ago, and a dozen ssmaller nationss arose from itss corpsse. Sseveruss, my sson Draco'ss godfather, planss to go there, to bribe officialss there to reveal their ssecretss."

Then Salazar realized the horrifying implication.

-About twenty Muggle countries with weapons that invoke mass sacrifice rituals! What is worse, they are definitely not friends with each other, since otherwise there would only be one nation in the world.

Salazar almost shuddered. Then he remembered Greek Fire, and the stupid wizards who made Greek Fire usable by Muggles. "How? When? Which wizard wass sstupid enough to let Muggless know of ssuch ritualss?"

Lucius was first genuinely confused by Salazar's questions, then dawning apprehension and open hatred appeared on his face. "I am not certain who the traitor wass. I know the weapon wass firsst ussed by Muggless about fifty yearss ago, when there wass a war in both the Muggle and the wizarding worldss."

Then, Lucius briefly explained the war with Grindelwald in Parseltongue with occasional vernacular for concepts not included in Parseltongue. Lucius explained Grindelwald's rise to power, the rumor that Grindelwald used Muggle sacrifices supplied by his Muggle allies to make himself invincible, how wizards from Great Britain, the United States of America, the Soviet Union, and a number of other countries joined forces against German, Italian and Japanese wizards, and how Albus Dumbledore defeated Grindelwald after Muggle Germany was defeated.

"A few dayss after hiss victory, the Muggle-loving former transfiguration teacher became sschoolmasster, and holder of the Line of Merlin Unbroken. If my memory iss correct, the Muggle country acrosss Atlantic ussed the ritual-weapon on its enemy in Far Easst sseveral monthss after that." For a moment, Lucius' face contorted with hatred and disgust, then he set his face, adding slowly, "Wizardss acrosss the Atlantic and in Easstern Europe allied with Muggless even after the war. Sseveruss ssaid Muggle nationss and wizardss there ussed mudbloodss to do magical tesstss, and that wass why many powerful lordss emerged during the passt sseveral decadess."

-Holder of Line of Merlin Unbroken, and a Muggle-loving fool, who might have taught Muggles the insanely powerful ritual that Merlin himself needed to sacrifice his life and magic to guard against.

This horrifying combination rendered Salazar completely speechless, and he was also outrageous toward the wizard named "Albus Dumbledore", who according to Lucius, was locked in Time.

In his full-fledged fury, Salazar's radiating magic might have gone wild, for the dusty decks and empty chairs began to shake, and Lucius' face twitched in horror. Salazar realized this, took in a deep breath, and calmed down.

-What has happened is already so. I need to figure out how to take the weapons away from Muggles and most wizards.

-By the way, why did Lucius mention "German wizards", "Italian wizards", and "British wizards", as if wizards belong to certain Muggle countries? If that is the case, I need to select my helpers carefully if I want to steal the weapons from Muggles. If I want to steal the ritual-weapon from British Muggles, I may have to turn to wizards in other countries.

Salazar pondered the implications, and asked, "Iss allying with Muggless common nowadayss? Why do current wizardss identify themsselvess with Muggle countriess?"

Then Lucius started a long recounting of history, on how the Christian and Islamic Muggles had persecuted wizarding kind, how traitors in the International Confederation of Wizards had conspired with some secular Muggle governments so that secular Muggle powers could make the religious power look ridiculous, how the Malfoys had fought against the passing of The International Statute of Wizarding Secrecy, how the Wizarding Counsel in Britain had grasped more and more power while imposing the Statute of Secrecy onto the free-spirited wizarding kind, how the good-for-nothing wizards in Wizarding Counsel in Britain - and its equivalents elsewhere - had regular coordination with the very high-tops of the Muggle governments, and how these factors led to the formation of Ministries of Magic or their equivalents in every major Muggle country.

"The Ministry hass extended its power to where it doess not belong, - they have even gone to the ridiculouss length as to determine the thicknesss of cauldronss. Now, about sseventy percent of the total working adultss in Wizarding Britain have ssomething to do with the Ministry of Magic." Lucius concluded his recount on recent history with this shocking remark.

Salazar listened and listened. He could understand the motives of some wizards in each step, but the stupidity in its entirety was beyond his wildest imagination.

-How could wizards as a whole accept something more oppressive than the Muggle kings? What is worse, for every three wizards who do actual work, seven other wizards just join the "Ministry of Magic", and rob their products? How could a society be stable? In the name of Atlantis, I need to overthrow this ridiculous thing and form a better kind of ruling order. But then…

"No wizardss had tried to overthrow this farcce?" Salazar asked incredulously.

To this question, Lucius smiled bitterly, and described the rise and fall of Tom Riddle, whose was also known as You-Know-Who, and Lord Voldemort.

From Lucius' perspective, the rise of Tom Riddle made quite some sense to Salazar - Tom Riddle claimed that the decline in magic was caused by the influx of mudbloods and thinning of wizarding blood; and not to mention that the level of corruption and bureaucracy in the Ministry of Magic were astonishing.

Lucius explained that the taxes imposed on people who did real work were so high that many good old families were driven out of business, and international commerce declined every year. Then, of course, good purebloods who were irked by the Muggle-loving propaganda enforced by the Ministry, annoyed by the ridiculous regulations made up by the good-for-nothing officials, and stolen from by the hefty taxes imposed by the Ministry, joined Tom Riddle who called himself "Lord Voldemort" in his bid against the Ministry.

"In one casse, they impossed a sixty percent import taxx on wine and beer, because the ssmall plebeian brewerss, a lot of them mudbloodss and Muggle-loverss, yearned it. As a result, mosst European countriess impossed a sixty percent import taxx on wine and beer produced in Britain." Lucius seemed to have tried to stop himself, but something slipped out, maybe intentionally. "The middle-end Malfoy elf-made drinkss losst about seventy percent of businesss in the Continent for thiss reasson. How could I not be attracted by Riddle'ss ideass?"

-Oh, Malfoys.

With a headache, Salazar remembered how efficient a lieutenant Armand had been when it had come to logistic matters, and how the first Draco could correctly convert between Galleons and Sickles before he could properly speak.

Salazar had to silently take in a breath, and reminded himself why he had agreed to Draco and Angitia's marriage: the snake animagus had stated in Parseltongue that he valued family more than money, and he wholeheartedly agreed with Salazar's idea on blood-purity.

-On the other hand, Tom Riddle's reasons against the Ministry of Magic and Lucius' alliance with him were indeed reasonable. Unfortunately for Lucius, I guess the Tom Riddles believed in nothing in particular.

Then, Lucius recounted the incredibly clever and efficient tactics used by You-Know-Who, and some of the confusing orders that Lucius had weaseled out of. "He ordered uss to kill all the Monroes including the house-elvess, except David, the sstrongesst. The old Lady Monroe wass againsst us, but her two ssonss were actually ssympathetic toward our causse. If we only asssasssinated the old woman, making it look like a natural death from old age, we could've had a noble housse on our sside, and let David fight with hiss father and uncle. Why terminate a pureblood old housse?Or if the Monroess had to be sacrificed to sserve as an example, why did he want to leave the sstrongesst unsscathed? "

Salazar knew the answer the instant he heard about the story: it was because this "David Monroe" was actually another Tom Riddle.

-This is completely insane. The Muggles have weapons with the power of mass sacrifice, and the most powerful wizard of the last two centuries has a hobby of splitting himself and fighting with himself. I wonder why the world is still largely intact at this moment.

Salazar wasn't surprised at all when Lucius mentioned a few occasions when Tom Riddle had refused to take advice from Lucius and others that might have led to an instant victory.

Lucius recounted the loss of Narcissa, his former lord's cold laugh and refusal for revenge. "I wass heart-broken, angry, confused, and afraid. I realized that he wouldn't look after any of our familiess in casse we died for the causse, and I wass the only protection that Draco had. I tried to sstay home ass much ass posssible, and kept Draco in my armss every night. The burn markss in my bedroom were a consstant reminder of my misstake and what it had cost me."

Salazar saw the glistening in Lucius' eyes, and knew the game Lucius was trying to play now - the use of real emotions, an advanced technique - yet it did gain a few points for Lucius, and it increased Salazar's loathing toward Tom Riddle, for this Tom Riddle was completely unworthy as a leader of any kind.

Before Salazar grew any impatience toward the sentimental things, Lucius began to describe the disappearance of the Dark Lord on the Halloween of 1981, and glossed over the ten years before Draco met Harry Potter.

"After what sseemed like the mudblood girl had tried to kill Draco - now I ssusspect the Dark Lord framed her - I brought Draco home." Lucius' face was quite confused by this point. "What I found shocked me. The-Boy-Who-Lived had talked Draco into believing outrageouss liess, such asss mudbloodss were no different from uss, yet I later got a feeling that he did thiss for good purposess, such as to deter Draco from doing thingss that could offend Muggless. He gave Draco bookss that depicted the power and knowledge of current Muggless, that Muggless had sent people to the moon, and Muggle'ss advanced knowledge in asstronomy."

-And that was why Lucius mentioned "Muggles" in the first place, and all the later talks about the ritual-weapon. He wanted to deter me from killing Muggles before knowing what they are capable of.

-Well, what Lucius did was the right thing to do. I might have killed Muggles unwittingly if I did not know, and my actions might lead to disasters for the wizarding kind. To be fair, Lucius did this with the clear knowledge that I despise Muggles and mudbloods, and he might have anticipated punishment for bringing the bad news. Luckily for him, I am better than that.

Salazar nodded to Lucius, encouraging him to speak on.

Lucius delineated the meeting between the Malfoys and Harry Potter in Gringotts, and, more importantly, the night one year before, especially the Unbreakable Vow that had took much of his magic.

"The contentss of the Vow are ass followss: 'I vow that I sshall not by any act of mine destroy the world. I shall take no chances in not destroying the world. If my hand iss forced, I may take the coursse of lessser desstruction over greater desstruction unlesss it sseems to me that thiss Vow itsself leadss to the world's end, and the friend in whom I have confided honesstly agreess that thiss iss sso. By my own free will, sso sshall it be.'" Lucius recounted the exact words with a white face, as if both horrified by the implication of the Unbreakable Vow, and missing his magic lost in it. He took in a deep breath, "Later, the Dark Lord's wordss in Parsseltongue stated that he wass convinced that there wass a Prophecy that if thingss around that boy went wrong, he might desstroy the world. And the Dark Lord and the Boy-Who-Lived discussed in Parsseltongue about the ability of the boy to desstroy the world, and both believed the boy wass capable of ssuch thingss, and the boy threatened the Dark Lord in Parsseltongue with huge explosionss that could kill all of uss, and he could accept no lesss than the Dark Lord'ss 'promisse to treat nationss kindly under your rule'. Then, I ssaw my headless body dropping to the ground, and I died, perhaps alongsside thirty-five other Death Eaterss."

Salazar had to slow down to absorb the implications of this, and Lucius promptly stopped talking.

-The older Tom Riddle believed that there was a Prophecy that the younger one might destroy the world, and both believed the younger one was capable of it. For whatever reason, the younger one truly believed that he wanted nice things for the world.

What a delight! Salazar thought sarcastically. First, my most powerful descendant is insane; and second, the world might be destroyed by one version of him. I need to figure out what happened, and then literally save the world from destruction.

-Seeing it from this point of view, I can understand why Lucius is so willing to cooperate in the younger Tom Riddle's plots, because Lucius doesn't want to destroy the world. Moreover, Lucius might have actually saved the world from my potential mistakes. I need to reward him, but I can't free him from the Tom Riddles immediately, for that might complicate matters.

Salazar sized Lucius up again, and said, "You have truly done well, Lucius, descendant of Draco and Angitia."

Lucius seemed to be surprised by Salazar's praise, and then his eyes dilated and his lips trembled.

-Oh, for the sake of Atlantis, what have you done to your subordinates, Tom Riddle!

Salazar was greatly annoyed by Lucius' expectation of death, and added another account of crime to Tom Riddle. "I mean you no harm."

As Lucius calmed down, or appeared to, Salazar reached into one of his pouches, obtained Rowena's Diadem, and put it onto the ground in front of Lucius. "I want your help to cleanse the dirt of death magic on Rowena's Diadem. And -" Salazar reached into his other pouch, and retrieved an oak wand from his hair-wand collections, "Thiss iss wand made from Armand'ss hair, that I occasionally usse. You should be able to usse it."

Salazar threw the wand with a core of Armand's hair onto the ground in front of Lucius, waved his own wand, and freed Lucius from his magical binding. "Usse the improved Guardian Charm on the Diadem."

-I need to observe for myself on how Lucius uses it, in case he knows more about it from the vernacular instructions Severus gave.

The blond man slowly stretched his limbs, being careful not to cause any misunderstandings, gingerly picked up the oak wand, and cast. "Expecto Patronum!"

To Salazar's slight dismay, a white ball no brighter than Salazar's own improved Patronus formed from Lucius' wand tip.

-Lucius probably has the same level of understanding of the charm as I do.

However, the advanced Patronus did seem to have life magic in it. As the residue of death magic on the Diadem was slowly removed, the sapphire and amber on the Diadem began to shine.

Salazar pondered further on the improved Patronus, and the new shielding charm that had been circling at the back of his mind for several hours. "I shall need your help in tessting one of my newesst inventionss. Afterwardss, you may keep some hintss about thiss charm. - By the way, keep practissing powerful magic, for you are sstill young, and raw magical power can grow until you are one-hundred years old."